1999年万圣节
你扮的是什么?狗还是奶牛?
What are you? A dog or a cow?
I'm a dog, but not just a dog.
我扮的是狗 但不是普通的狗
是一只勃起的狗 你们看
I'm a dog with a boner. Check it out!
Well, there it is. Is the poop ready?
好了 就是那栋
大便准备好了吗?
That's a roger on the poop.
当然准备好了
Oh, holy crap, how big was that dog?
天啊 多大的狗拉出来的啊?
小狗 但有七只
Small, but there was seven of them.
I'll give you three reasons why this is a bad idea.
我会给你们罗列三个理由 来解释为什么这不是好主意
第一 警察 第二 狗 第三 前门的美国步枪协会海报
One, cops. Two, dogs.
Three, NRA front door.
若你能看清这句话 那说明你在射击范围内
别担心了 迪恩 这些人自找的
Quit worrying, Dean. These people deserve it.
他们从不发糖果
They never give out candy.
记得我们上次执行这种任务吗?
Yeah, but remember last time we pulled something like this?
迪恩的胳膊断了
Dean got his arm broke.
那是因为他一个人跑了 然后掉进了沟里
That's because he ran off alone and fell in a ditch.
要是他一直跟我们在一起 就不会有事
If he just sticks with us, he'll be fine.
Come on! Let's do this.
来吧 我们动手吧
Okay...
好吧
-  - Go!
走
Ahh, uh-oh...
火变大了
It's getting kinda big-ish.
糟了!
- Come on! - Quick!
不行!
No!
屎溅到嘴里了!
Doo-doo in mouth! Doo-doo in mouth!
我们离开这儿
Let's get out of here!
不行 屋里有人
We can't - there's people in there!
别开枪!稻草人烧了你的房子!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
The scarecrow set your house on fire.
家里没人!我们得打911!
No one's home. We gotta call 911!
兄弟 你真的反应过度了
Dude! You're seriously overreacting.
天...
Call 911!
打911!
看啊 他们给了糖的
Hey, look! They do give out candy.
我们死定了!
We're so dead!
天啊!我爸会杀了我
Oh, my God! My father's going to kill me.
快 我们走 我们离开这里
Come on, let's go. Let's get out of here.
Wait! Wait a second, I got an idea.
等等!等一下 我有办法了
谁有笔?
- Who's got a pen? - Use Wes's dick!
用韦斯的鸡巴!
Quick! Give me a first name.
- 快 给我一个名字 - 宙斯
Zeus!
A kid's name!
一个孩子的名字
- 瑞奇! - 好的
- Ricky! - Okay.
现在想个姓氏
Now a last name.
有了 斯坦顿
I got it! Stanton.
好的
等等 不行!什么?那是我的姓氏
Wait, no! What? That's my last name.
那又如何?你又不叫瑞奇
So? Your first name's not Ricky.
快点!
- Come on. - Come on.
Go!
走吧!
-  -
Check this out.
看看这个
笨小孩恶作剧时把他的夹克衫点着了
Numb-nuts kid caught his jacket on fire during his prank.
最搞笑的是 他妈把他的名字写在了衣领上
Here's the best part.
His mommy wrote his name on the collar.
'Ricky Stanicky'?
“瑞奇斯坦尼奇”?好蠢
Dumb shit.
坏消息 警长
Bad news, Chief. Just heard back.
学区刚回话说没有叫斯坦尼奇的
No Stanickys in the school district.
一定是外地来的孩子
Kid must be from out of town.
真烦人
Shit.
I can't believe that actually worked.
我不敢相信真的蒙混过关了
Guys, I think we just made a friend for life.
各位 我们刚刚交了一个终身好友
瑞奇·斯坦尼奇
瑞奇斯坦尼奇做的!
是斯坦尼奇!
瑞奇斯坦尼奇来过
♪ Then I put my codes ♪
♪ In the machine ♪
斯坦尼奇做的!
♪ But the world I found ♪
♪ Was made of faulty dreams ♪
♪ Of faulty dreams ♪
♪ Fairy-like companions ♪
是斯坦尼奇!
♪ To the dark maths That catapult ♪
♪ Us into imagined worlds ♪
是斯坦尼奇开的车!
♪ Seems a mockery remote ♪
现如今
Want to grab a quick drink?
想快速喝一杯吗?
欢迎宝宝惠特克的到来
你为什么要快速喝一杯?
Why would you have a quick drink...
瑞奇:给我打电话
...when you can have the long drink?
明明你可以慢慢喝一杯
在地球上最幸福的国度芬兰 我们发明了长饮
In Finland, the happiest country on Earth,
we invented the long drink...
车库里的啤酒就这么多了 我们要出去再买点吗?
That's it for the beer in the garage.
Do we need to run out and get more?
不用 足够了
No. That's perfect.
你确定?
You sure?
- 确定 这地方看起来太棒了 - 是吗?
- Yeah. The place looks amazing. - Yeah?
也许对我们来说 这会是一个很棒的副业
Maybe this would be a good side hustle for us.
“艾琳和迪恩的迎婴派对”
Erin and Dean's baby showers.
- 真不错 - 是啊
- I like it. - Yeah.
就在那时 吉尔伯特盖恩斯意识到 解决帮派暴力问题的答案
And that's when Gilbert Gines realized
that the answer to gang violence
可能隐藏在一把破旧的小号阀门里
may be found in the spit-valve of a well-worn trumpet.
- 这什么节目? - 是一个叫《本周英雄》的节目
What is this?
Uh, it's a show called 'Hero of the Week'.
专门报道那些身怀绝技的普通人
It's about everyday people who do these incredible things.
我的制片人想让我报名参加 他说他在那节目组有熟人
My producer at Channel 6 wants me to submit for it.
He says he has a good contact there.
Well, what are you waiting for?
那你还在等什么?
Well, if I want MFMBC to notice me,
如果我想让MFMBC台注意到我 那我需要更好的故事
what I need are better assignments,
但我只有这些 一点都不重要的婴儿级新闻
but all I get are these babies-who-Tweet stories.
Mm!
Speaking of babies,
说到婴儿 你能帮我把这些照片挂起来吗?
can you please hang these pictures up for me, over there.
- 挂那边 - 好的
It's JT and Susan's baby pictures.
是JT和苏珊婴儿时期的照片
天啊 JT出生时就有恒齿?
Jesus, God! Was JT born with adult teeth?
拜托 他的牙齿很可爱 看看那个
Oh, come on, his teeth are cute. Look at that.
可爱?他看起来像乡巴佬希特勒
Cute? He looks like hillbilly Hitler.
- 你觉得所有婴儿都很可爱 - 确实所有婴儿都很可爱
- You think all babies are cute. - All babies are cute.
是的呢
Yeah, sure.
遥控器像是粘了二十年一样
And the remotes are sticky for like 20 years.
Well, there are good things
生孩子也有好的一面
about having kids too, you know.
- 真的吗? - 是啊
- Really? - Yeah.
我不记得我父母有这种感觉
I don't remember my parents feeling that way.
你不觉得你的父母 很享受养孩子的过程?
You don't think your parents enjoyed having kids?
It doesn't matter. What we have is way better.
不重要
我们所拥有的好多了 我们一直这么说
It's what we always talked about.
Hmm.
我爱你
I love you.
你爱我
You love me.
- We love Paul. - Hmm.
我们爱保罗
- And we don't need anyone else. -
我们不需要其他人
天啊 JT 别管我
Oh, my God! JT, leave me alone!
这是我的迎婴派对 我要喝一杯 就一杯
It is my baby shower, I'm going to have one drink. One!
栗原医生说这完全没问题 你们好
Dr. Kurihara said it is perfectly fine. Hello.
Dr. Kurihara is part of the medical industrial complex,
栗原医生是医疗产业综合体中的一员
而助产士玛吉说你要吃素
and Midwife Maggie said you're on a strict vegan diet
并且必须滴酒不沾
and absolutely no alcohol.
好的 你不是助产士玛吉 你是我的丈夫
Okay, well you are not Midwife Maggie, you are my husband.
对 我知道 但我也是产妇陪护爸爸 那是我的工作
Yeah, I know, but I'm also Daddy Doula.
- That's my job. - You gotta stop saying that.
别这么说 你会让宝宝吐出来的
You're going to make the baby throw up.
他们会吐在里面吗?
They can't... Can they throw up inside of there?
等等 JT是你的产妇陪护?
Wait, JT's your doula?
是的 宝宝出生时 他也想裸着
Yeah, he also wants to be naked when the baby is born.
- Don't you? - I don't want to be naked.
我不想裸着
我只想脱掉衬衫 在第一次抱孩子时肌肤相亲
I just want my shirt off, okay,
for the first embrace, skin to skin.
这样可以建立亲密联系 好吧
- It's a bonding thing. -
- 很好 - 你最好接电话
- Good. - Hey, you better get that.
这是20分钟内 瑞奇第四次打来电话了
That's the fourth time Ricky called in, like, 20 minutes.
看看他想干什么 他一整天都在给我打电话
Yeah, see what he wants, man.
He's been blowing me up all day.
- Really? -  Yeah.
- 真的吗? - 是的
All right.
好吧
斯坦尼奇 你好啊 还好吗?
Stanicky! What up, man? How's it going?
我给你倒茶 不倒酒 别喝酒
I'm going to get you a tea, not wine, don't drink.
嗯 我现在正忙着呢 我...
Yeah, hey I'm in the middle of something right now. I just...
Are you serious?
你是说真的?
Uh-huh. Okay.
好的
Well, just do me a favor and have someone call me
帮我一个忙
你做完手术以后 让人给我打电话 好吗?
when you get out of surgery, all right?
So you're all alone?
所以你一个人?
Shit, man, that sucks.
兄弟 那太糟了
好吧 坚持住
All right, hang in there.
We'll all be sending you positive vibes
我们都会在这里 给你精神上的支持 伙计
from over here, buddy.
Love you too, man.
我也爱你
What's going on? What did he say?
怎么了?他说什么?
回来了
It's back.
- 什么回来了? - 癌症
What's back?
- The cancer. - Oh, God.
天啊 我还以为他的癌症已经好了
I thought he was out of the woods.
可怜虫
Poor guy.
他们得切除他的另一个睾丸吗?
Are they going to have to remove the...
...other testicle?
他们能这么做吗? 我以为人需要至少一个才能生存
And can they even do that?
I thought you needed at least one to live.
什么?不 那是肾 笨蛋
What? No! That's kidneys, dumbo.
Where is he?
他在哪儿?
他在奥尔巴尼的一家医院里
He's in a hospital in Albany.
奥尔巴尼?他为什么在奥尔巴尼?
Albany? Why is he in Albany?
He flew in from Nairobi to meet with some non-profits
他从内罗毕飞去 见一些非营利组织的人
and he had an attack.
然后他病情发作了
他们今晚就给他做手术
They're gonna open him up tonight.
你应该开车过去 那个可怜虫孤身一人
Dean, you should drive out there.
The poor guy's all alone.
我不能去 不然迎婴派对怎么办?
I can't go tonight. What about the baby shower?
萨默海耶斯也会来
And Summerhayes is going to be here.
你担心你老板? 拜托 他只是同事而已
What? You're worried about your boss?
Come on, he's just business.
在你们整个人生中 瑞奇都在你们身边支持你们
Ricky's been there for you guys your whole lives.
Dude, just go. I've got Summerhayes covered.
兄弟 你去吧 我来接待萨默海耶斯
什么?不
What? No, no, no, no.
你应该打电话告诉他 你家里有紧急情况
You should call him
and tell him you have a family emergency.
你应该跟迪恩一起去
You should go with Dean.
你说真的?我们不能同时抛弃老板
Are you serious? Babe, we can't both bail on the boss.
你可以
Yes! Yes, you can.
可能不必参加迎婴派对 还会让他松了一口气呢
I mean, he'll probably be relieved
that he doesn't have to go to a baby shower.
Well, looks like we're going to Albany.
看来我们要去奥尔巴尼了
你说得对 提起萨默海耶斯 简直是神来之笔
You were right, man -
the Summerhayes thing totally put it over the top.
The Devil's in the details, my friend.
细节决定成败
What the hell took y'all so long?
你们怎么这么久才来? 飞机一小时后起飞
- The flight leaves in an hour. - Oh, sorry.
我们执行了出色的临时计划 做了所有工作
We were doing all the work
executing our brilliant last-minute plan.
斯坦尼奇的电话是谁打的?
Who made the Stanicky calls?
谁在乎谁做了什么? 重点是计划奏效了
Who cares who did what, Wes? The point is it worked.
We got out of a baby shower,
我们刚从迎婴派对中溜出来 而且还拿到了马克雷比莱的门票!
and we got tickets to Marc-fucking-Rebillet!
-  - Whoo!
你们怎么拿到票的?
- How'd you score those babies? - Yeah, this guy we work with
我们的一个同事昨晚双脚踝骨折了
broke one of his ankles last night.
He fell out of a tree trying to get his kid's balloon.
他试着拿孩子的气球时 从树上摔了下来
- 可怜虫 - 我们拿到了他的票
- Poor guy. - So we got his tickets.
Goddamn, y'all so lucky, man!
天啊 你们太幸运了
你们总是走狗屎运
This kind of shit happens to you all the time.
这叫好人有好报
Hey! Good things happen to good people.
没错 大西洋城 我们来了
That's right. Atlantic City, here we come.
我们好好享受新泽西之旅吧!
Let's tear New Jersey a new armpit!
Whoa!
这不一样 但感觉也很好
It's not the same but it feels just as good.
你只需要侧着身子做爱 像海象一样
I mean, you just have to have sex on the side like a walrus.
那样不会把宝宝的头撞扁吗?
Won't that dent the baby's head?
I had a friend named Liam, and his head got all dick-dented.
我有个叫利亚姆的朋友 他的头就被鸡巴撞扁了
I think maybe his mother had a short vagina.
我觉得他妈的阴道可能很短
只是有点担心宝宝惠特克
Just looking out for baby Whitaker.
- 你还是要用惠特克这个名字吗? - 是啊 这名字很常见
So you still going with Whitaker, huh?
We are! It's a family name. All right?
- 好名字 - 嗯 谢谢
- Oh, that's nice. -  Yeah, thank you.
You guys know the rules.
你们知道规矩 电话关机 以免被跟踪
Phones off, so we don't get tracked.
- Mm-hm. - Yep.
好
- All right. Wes. - I'm Wes.
好的 韦斯
- 我是韦斯 - 拿出圣经
- Bible! - Ooh.
All right...
好的 我们有什么?
What we got?
瑞奇的癌症又发作了
- Ricky's cancer's back. - Oh, no.
- 太糟了 - 是的
Emergency surgery in Albany.
在奥尔巴尼做紧急手术
太糟了 “紧急手术...”
Oh, that's terrible. Emergency surgery...
等等 为什么一定要是癌症?
Hey, why does it have to be cancer?
大家不会担心吗? 我们还得再做化疗吗?
Like, won't everybody get worried?
That mean I gotta do chemo again?
是的 我们可以利用这个借口 直接去看世界职业棒球大赛
Yeah, and that's going to take us right into the World Series.
- Ahh. - Boom!
赞!
All right, one final bit of business before we land.
好的 着陆之前最后一点正事
斯坦尼奇的电话拿出来 我们来发照片墙吧
Stanicky phone. Let's get this Instagram out of the way.
好的
There we go.
-"Life is precious." - It is.
“生命诚可贵”
- 的确 -“友谊价更高”
-"And so is friendship." - Hmm.
"Thanks to my boys for being here for me."
“感谢我的朋友们前来支持我”
- 很好 - 好的 弄完了吗?
Good.
All right, are we done? Is it get drunk time?
- 该喝酒了吧? - 好
- Yeah. - A toast!
举杯 敬瑞奇斯坦尼奇
To Ricky Stanicky.
敬瑞奇斯坦尼奇
The best friend we never had.
我们从未有过的最好的朋友
Yoo!
金三叉戟
马克雷比莱仅限一晚(已售罄)
从床上滚下来 贱人 快滚
♪ Get the fuck out of bed Bitch, go! ♪
-  -
♪ Get up, get up! You gotta go, gah! ♪
起来 起来 起来 快走
♪ Wake up, time to wake up Bitch, get up! ♪
醒醒 该醒醒了 贱人 起来
-  -
-  -  Woo-hoo-hoo!
- 好啊 - 天啊 这太棒了!
God, that was good! That was amazing!
太精彩了!感谢瑞奇斯坦尼奇!
- Thank you, Ricky Stanicky. - The fucking Loop Daddy!
- 那段循环!耶! - 难以置信 伙计!
Unbelievable, dude.
我的负罪感全都值了
It makes all that guilt I'm feeling totally worthwhile.
- 是啊 - 我们为什么要有负罪感?
Why do we even have to feel guilt?
我们本来可以直接告诉她们 就不用有什么顾虑了
We could have just told them.
You know, and cut out that whole angst part.
不行 因为雷比莱的门票 是我们今早意外得到的
No, because the Rebillet tickets
fell into our lap this morning,
女孩们几周前就计划好了派对
and the girls have had the baby shower planned for weeks.
是啊 但她们都是坚强的女人
Yeah. Yeah, but they're strong women.
I'm sure they would've gotten over
她们肯定会原谅我们错过小派对的
us skipping one little party.
这可不是小派对 这是我的孩子的迎婴派对
It's not one little party. It's my baby shower.
Oh, a Jack and Coke.
我要威士忌加可乐
我要一杯双X啤酒 谢谢
I'll have a Dos Equis, please. Hoo!
Do you have, uh... do you have organic vodka?
你们有有机伏特加吗?
Just any vodka, it's all...
- 随便什么伏特加都行 都...都可以 - 谢谢
- Anything. - Thank you.
Speaking of vodka, I'll take a Belvedere, neat,
说起来 我要雪树伏特加 纯的 还要一盘鱿鱼圈
and a plate of your crispiest calamari.
不行 罗德 不行 这么不对
No, no, Rod. No! Bad!
You keep freeloading off the customers
你一直利用顾客在这里白吃白喝 你给我出去
and you're out of here.
他喜欢找我麻烦
He loves giving me the business.
我只是说清楚 我绝不是占便宜的人
Just to be clear, I'm anything but a freeloader.
Just going to give you guys a little 'squid pro quo'
我本来想跟你们鱿鱼换鱿鱼
for the calamari.
真的吗?什么意思?
Really? Meaning?
我在斯洛特沼泽赌场做午夜表演
Oh, I do a midnight show at the Slot Swamp Casino.
I'll get you guys in, half price.
我会带你们进去 只需半价
什么表演?
- What kind of show? - Ah. Check this out.
看看这个
- 砰 - 天啊!
Boom!
Oh, shit! Yo!
“硬摇滚罗德 南泽西州 首屈一指的限制级摇滚模仿者”
"Rock Hard Rod -
"South Jersey's premier X-rated rock'n'roll impersonator".
这并不像听起来那么疯狂
That's not as crazy as it sounds.
I mean, most of the songs are just about masturbation,
不过大多数歌曲是关于自慰的
我们都会自慰 对吧?
and we all do that, right?
Yeah!
- 是的! - 真酷
Actually, Rod, I don't think we'll be able to make the show,
我觉得我们没法去看表演
但如果你放下你打飞机的手 我们会请你喝一杯
but we'll buy you a drink
if you put your jerk-off hand down.
You drive a hard bargain, sir.
你可真会讨价还价
So, you do a bunch of jerk-off songs to make a living?
所以你靠唱小黄曲谋生?
是的 我会做全套动作
Yeah, I do a whole act.
连续地 从头到尾 精液流淌
Wall-to-wall, top-to-bottom jizz jams!
你会惊讶地发现很多歌都适合
You'll be surprised at how much material lends itself to it.
I mean, 'Beat It', Michael Jackson.
迈克尔杰克逊的《避开》
'Wind Beneath My Wings', Bette Midler.
贝特迈德尔的《风中的翅膀》 The Strokes的所有歌
- Anything by The Strokes! - Mm.
我是世界上唯一一个发现此事的人
Yeah, and I'm the only one in the world
that's figured it out.
- 是啊 这很难让人相信 - 是啊
Yeah, it's almost hard to believe.
巴里 我亲爱的朋友们会请我喝酒
Oh, Barry, my dear friends here
will buy me that drink after all.
我也会模仿 给我出题吧 我什么都会 我是训练有素的演员
Oh, yeah, I also do impressions.
You name it, I can do it. I'm a trained actor, you know.
- 我有一个好题目 - 嗯
- I got a good one for you, Rod. - Yeah?
不如你模仿一下 我叫保安之前赶紧离开的人吧
Why don't you do the guy that gets the fuck out of here
before I call security?
不用 没事
No, no, no, it's okay. It's okay.
我们很想看看 你给他上酒吧
I think we'd like to see this.
And go ahead and bring him that drink.
Ha! And the calamari, Bar-ry!
还有鱿鱼圈 巴里
Dickhead! Love that guy.
笨蛋 我喜欢那家伙
So, who do you guys want me to do?
那么你们想让我模仿谁? 你们喜欢欧文威尔逊吗?
You, er, I don't know, you like Owen Wilson?
- Sure. - We love Owen Wilson.
我们喜欢欧文威尔逊
- 是啊 那可以 - 我想看看欧文威尔逊
- Yeah, that's fine. - I would love some Owen Wilson.
Wow!
你们凭什么认为
Where in the history of our relationship
did you think I couldn't do an impersonation
我模仿不了像大欧那么可爱的人呢?
of somebody as adorable as The Big O?
That is an excellent Owen Wilson. That's a good Owen.
模仿得太像欧文威尔逊了 太厉害了
- It's okay. - Wow.
还好吧 没那么好
-  It's not that good. - Thank you. Oh, er...
谢谢 让我...
- I'm just... -  Calamari's here, man.
鱿鱼圈来了
好的 一个老梗 但很精彩
All right, an oldie but a goodie.
Take a look at this tit, kid.
看看这个乳房 孩子!
可能是你这辈子剩下的时间里 会看到的最后一个
Probably the last one you're ever going to see
for the rest of your life.
Don't drink no more, Momma.
妈妈 别再喝酒了 你喝了酒以后会变得很刻薄
You're real mean when you drink stuff.
别再抱怨了 邋遢鬼
Quit your bitchin', ya sloppy punk.
你想知道你是怎么来的吗? 你老爸操了我的屁眼
You wanna know how you was hatched?
Your old man was basting my rump roast
然后有些精液流进了我的阴道
and some of it dribbled into my woolly burger.
You know what that makes you?
知道这让你变成什么吗?大便婴儿
A shit baby!
没错 你就是坨大便 而且永远都是!
That's right, you're nothing but shit,
and you always will be!
Is... is that from 'Downton Abbey'?
是《唐顿庄园》里的吗?
不 是...
That was, er...
just a little skit from my childhood.
我只是演了我小时候的一段场景
Er, yeah...
嗯
I think it's time to hit the tables, boys. Huh?
各位 我觉得 是时候上赌桌了 对吧?
Right on. Where are we going?
没错 我们去哪儿?
铜帽是唯一设有50美分赌桌的赌场
Copper Bonnet's the only place on the boardwalk
with 50-cent tables.
没那么多妓女 但她们更友好
Not as many hookers, but they're friendlier -
they don't get weirded out
要是你给她们梳头 她们不会被吓到
when you just wanna brush their hair.
罗德 我觉得我们就待在这里
Yeah, Rod, I think we're just going to stay around here.
Oh, here's great. I'm friends with the bartender, Barry.
这儿很不错 我和调酒师巴里是朋友
嘿 “硬挺”罗尼 我们在自寻乐子
Hey, Hard-on Ronnie, we are doing our own thing.
我们得继续聊我们的 可能只能让你一个人待着了
We got our thing going on,
and we're probably just gonna...
leave you.
Okay, I can take a hint.
好的 我懂你的意思
你们看着我 觉得我的模仿水平很烂 对吧?
You guys look at me
and you just see another scumbag impersonator, right?
谢谢理解 兄弟 你是一个好人
Thanks for understanding, man. You're a good dude.
- 什么鬼 伙计? - 怎么了?
- What the hell, man? - What?
你说话不必这么刻薄
You didn't have to be so mean about it.
什么?我没刻薄啊 我干什么了?
What? I wasn't... What did I do?
什么?我刚刚的行为很混蛋吗?
What? Was I being an asshole?
你叫他“硬挺罗尼” 是“硬摇滚罗德”
Well, you called him 'Hard-on Ronnie'.
It's 'Rock Hard Rod'.
对哦 对不起
Ohh, right, I'm so sorry.
I didn't know Weird Al Wankovic
我不知道怪人自摸先生这么敏感
would be so sensitive.
罗德 嘿 罗德
Rod! Hey, Rod!
These are mine.
这些是我的
I just wanted to say sorry for what happened back there.
我只是想为刚才的事道歉
My friends...
我的朋友们 他们只是希望 我们三个人重聚
they just want it to be some kind of reunion, just us,
但那样不礼貌 所以...
but that wasn't cool, so...
没事 我理解 这种事经常发生
Whatever, I get it. Happens all the time.
你们开着丰田亚洲龙来到大西洋城
You guys come in to AC
with your Toyota Avalons and your anesthesiologist money.
带着你们做麻醉师赚的钱
Strutting around like a bunch of big shots.
像大人物一样昂首阔步地走着 我跟你说
Let me tell you something.
因为你们这些混蛋 我们失去了琼里弗斯和迈克尔杰克逊
We lost Joan Rivers and Michael Jackson
because of you fuckers, okay?
我们都不是麻醉师
None of us are anesthesiologists.
- 你们不是来参加大会的吗? - 不是
Not here for the convention?
No.
我理解 兄弟
Hey, I get it, man.
你看着我 就像看到了 一个马戏团怪人一样 对吧?
You look at me and see another asshole sideshow freak, right?
- 不是的 - 我的能力不止此
- Not at all. - I'm more than that.
I'm a damn good actor.
我是一个非常厉害的演员
你会知道的
You'll see.
Shit!
糟了
Who are they?
他们是谁?
我想避开的疯狂粉丝
Crazy fans I was trying to avoid.
总之 我得走了 拿着我的名片
Anyway, I gotta run. Hey, take my card.
记住这个名字
Remember that name.
我保证总有一天 你会用得上的
I promise it's going to mean something to you some day.
I would not be surprised.
我不会惊讶
Oh! Jeez.
天啊!
Oh, my God! Yes! Yes!
天啊 好耶!棒!
- 现在把我的钱给我! - JT!
- Give me my money right now! - JT! JT!
现在别烦我 迪恩!我火力全开!
Not now, Dean. I'm on fire!
这一次 我会以胜者的姿态 离开大西洋城!
And for once I'm going to leave Atlantic City a winner!
苏珊要生了
Susan's in labor.
这不是一个好主意 我就知道这不是一个好主意
This was a bad idea. I knew this was a bad idea.
别这样 兄弟 你这是事后诸葛亮
Don't friggin' do that, man.
You're 'Monday morning quarterbacking' right now.
谁知道她会提前六周分娩?
Who could've figured she'd go into labor six weeks early?
六周
Six weeks! My baby's going to be born six weeks early.
我的宝宝会早产六周 他会没事吧?
- Is he going to be okay? - The baby's going to fine.
宝宝会没事的 宝宝总是早产六周
Babies are born six weeks early all the time.
我就早产了六周
I was born six weeks early.
见鬼!快走!
Oh, shit! Go, go, go! Go!
普罗维登斯分娩中心
苏珊莱文 她在哪个病房?
Susan Levine. What room is she in?
- 莱文? - 对 莱文
- Levine? - Yeah, Levine.
Ah, here we are. She and the baby are in 208.
找到了 她和宝宝在208室
She had the baby?!
她已经生了
Oh, baby Whitaker.
宝宝惠特克
我给你准备的生育计划不是这样的
This was not the birth plan I had for you.
我想让你出生在葛斯威恩海滩上
I wanted you born on the shores of Goosewing Beach.
你知道我的生育计划是什么吗? 就是让你在这里
You know what my birth plan was?
For you to actually be here.
Why isn't he wearing a shirt?
他为什么不穿衬衫?
我正在跟我的儿子利昂娜 进行肌肤接触
I'm having skin-to-skin contact with my son, Leona.
这是一种行之有效的 调节婴儿体温的方法 可以让他平静
It's a proven way of regulating a newborn baby's temperature,
and it calms him, thank you.
用毯子不就行了?
Don't blankets do that?
他真是个小可爱
Oh, he is such a little peanut.
我们应该叫他小虾米 他真是个小可爱
We should call him Shrimpy, he's such a little peanut.
Please don't call my grandson 'Shrimpy'.
请别叫我的外孙小虾米
小虾米是海里的蟑螂
Shrimps are the cockroaches of the sea.
早产六周的婴儿体重能有接近三公斤 已经很好了 对吧 妈妈?
6lbs is pretty good for a month and a half early, right, Mom?
他很完美
Oh, he's perfect. He's perfect.
I want to know where the hell you guys were tonight.
我想知道你们今晚到底去哪儿了
We called every hospital in Albany
我们给奥尔巴尼所有医院都打了电话
根本没有瑞奇斯坦尼奇的记录
and there was no record of a Ricky Stanicky.
还有你上次跟我说 你去看他是因为他得了...
Yeah, and the last thing you tell me
is you got to go see him because he's got...
What kind of cancer?
哪种癌症?
Er... anal.
肛门
I thought it was testicular.
我以为是睾丸?
是睾丸 但癌症扩散到肛门了
It was testicular, but then it spread to his anus.
Yeah, they had to remove it.
对 医生不得不将其摘除
医生要摘除他的屁眼?
They removed his asshole?
Er... just the outer lip part.
只是外唇部分
外唇部分?他是狒狒吗?
Outer lip part? What is he, a fucking baboon?
拜托 韦斯 到底是什么情况? 你们去哪儿了?
Come on, Wes. What's going on here?
Where were you?
好吧
Okay.
这是一个谎言
It was a lie.
全都是谎言
It's all been a lie.
什么是谎言?
What's a lie?
The whole Ricky Stanicky thing.
整个瑞奇斯坦尼奇的事都是谎言
这是...假的
It was, uh...
It's bullshit.
JT, what's he talking about?
JT 他在说什么?
是啊 迪恩 他在说什么?
Yeah, Dean, what is he talking about?
他是说瑞奇斯坦尼奇 对我们撒谎了 好吗?
He's saying...
Ricky Stanicky lied to us.
Okay? There was no cancer.
他没得癌症
我们赶到医院时
When we got to the hospital, Ricky was standing out front
他站在香槟和豪华轿车前
with a bottle of champagne and a limo.
结果今天是他
Turns out that it was his five-year anniversary
being cancer free.
癌症康复五周年纪念日
所以他假装自己得了癌症
So he pretended to have cancer
只是为了庆祝他没了癌症?
just so he could celebrate not having cancer?
I... Yeah.
是的
瑞奇就是这种人 他有一种奇怪的幽默感
It's typical Rick.
You know, he's got such a weird sense of humour.
是的 没错
-  He does, yep. -  Okay...
他在奥尔巴尼 见“给予绿色”基金会的人
He was in Albany meeting with the Give Green Foundation,
然后我猜他想跟我们一起庆祝
and I guess he just wanted to celebrate with us.
所以他捉弄了我们
So he pranked us.
给予绿色基金会?
The Give Green Foundation?
对 你听说过他们吧 利昂娜? 他们很棒
Yeah. You've heard of them, Leona. They're wonderful.
等等 你们为什么不给我们打电话 告诉我们他没事
Wait, why didn't you call us and tell us that he was okay?
你们的手机为什么整晚关机?
And why was your phone off all night?
Oh, baby, it was a whirlwind.
我们遇到了突发事件 瑞奇带我们去看了一场单口喜剧表演
Ricky took us to a stand-up comedy show
他们不让我们带手机
and they didn't allow cell phones, so...
演出结束时已经很晚了
And after that, the night turned into a blur.
我本来想陪你生产的
You know I wanted to be here for you for this.
我比你更想陪着你
I wanted this more than you did.
别让孩子吸你的那玩意 把他交给他妈!
Oh, get that baby off that thing
and give him to his mother.
Oh, that is disgusting!
太恶心了!
不 分离很危险 让他吸
No. It's dangerous to detach. Let him suck it out.
Yeah. Good boy.
嗯 好孩子
这是胡说八道
This hippie-dippy crap.
我下周割礼仪式上见到瑞奇时 一定会给他一耳光
Well, I'm certainly going to give Ricky an earful
when I see him at the bris next week.
割礼仪式是什么?
What's a bris?
- 就是割包皮仪式 - 听起来像是一种汤
It's the circumcision ceremony.
Oh! It sounds like a soup.
You know, I doubt he's going to be able to be there, sadly.
很不幸 我不确定他能不能来
为什么不行?
Why not?
- 他要工作 在内罗毕 - 他不工作
He has work in Nairobi.
No, he doesn't.
韦斯周六晚上在普罗维登斯帮他筹款
Wes is helping him out with some fundraiser
in Providence on Saturday night.
I remember telling...  I told you.
我记得跟你们说过...我说过的
- 对 - 很好
Yeah.
Great. Well, the bris is on Sunday, so he can make it.
割礼是在周日 这样他就能来了
或许可以 除非他周日一早就要飞走
Yeah, maybe. Unless he's got to fly out early on Sunday.
那太荒唐了
Well, that's ridiculous.
如果他周六在城里
Come on, if he's in town on Saturday,
他为什么不多待一天 见见宝宝?
why wouldn't he spend an extra day to meet baby Whitaker?
Yeah, why wouldn't he?
就是 有何不可呢?
你说得太对了
You're absolutely right. He should stay an extra day.
他应该多待一天 我会确保他参加
In fact, I'm going to make sure of it.
- 搞什么 迪恩? - 你想让我说什么?
What the fuck, Dean?
What did you want me to say, man?
他们当时都盯着我 宝宝惠特尼在你身上吃奶
They were all staring at me.
I look at you. You've got baby Whitaker nursing on you.
顺便说一句 好可怕的名字
Horrible name, by the way.
- 我只是... - 你惊慌失措了
- I just-- - You panicked.
我惊慌失措?你说什么呢? 是你差点暴露了我们!
I panicked?!
What are you talk...?! You're the one who almost outed us!
你还擅自安排了斯坦尼奇的日程 他不是一个人的表演 你知道的
And you made plans with Stanicky!
Ricky Stanicky is not a one-man show. You know that!
这是一个需要精心维护的谎言
It's a fragile fabric, man.
瑞奇斯坦尼奇只能在三人团队中使用
Ricky Stanicky is only to be used as a three-man team.
那之前你说和瑞奇打高尔夫 好让JT找公司报销的事呢?
Huh.
So, what about the golf rounds with Ricky
that JT charged to your company?
- 你当时不在场 - 什么?
- You weren't there. - What?
我付了打高尔夫的费用 是因为你没钱
I charged the rounds of golf
because you didn't have any money.
Seriously, Wes. What happened in there, man?
说真的 韦斯 刚才是什么情况?
基思一直因为找工作、成天睡觉
Look.
Keith's been on my ass about finding a job,
还有在水槽上磨脚皮的事成天骂我
and sleeping all day...
and pumicing my foot-skin over the sink.
- 这跟斯坦尼奇有什么关系? - 我需要喘口气!
What the fuck does this have to do with Stanicky?
I needed a break!
基思有时让我很压抑
Keith can be very oppressive.
Sometimes I feel like I'm living
我有时觉得 自己活在《使女的故事》里
in a gay 'Handmaid's Tale'.
So I went to a pot farm, where they make cannabis milk.
所以我去了一个 生产大麻牛奶的大麻种植场
你谎称跟斯坦尼奇出去 好去喝大麻牛奶?
You played the Stanicky card to get pot milk?
You never had milk like this before.
- 你以前从没喝过这种牛奶 - 没有
- No, I haven't. - It's delicious.
- 很好喝 - 希望如此
I hope!
他们整天都给那些幸运的奶牛喂大麻
They must feed these lucky cows weed all day,
因为他们挤奶时 就会“砰”!
because when they milk 'em - boom!
梦中情奶
Dream cream!
What did you just say?
- 你刚刚说什么? - 梦中情奶
Dream cream.
Huh!
凯洛的家乡
我们完蛋了 彻底完蛋了
We're fucked. We're majorly fucked.
You know, we don't deserve this shit.
我们不应该落得这种下场 我们只是撒了一个谎而已
All we did was tell one lie.
很多年以来 撒了成百上千个
Hundreds and hundreds of times over many, many years.
或许他们会忘记 自己邀请了斯坦尼奇来参加割礼
Hey, maybe they'll forget
that they invited Stanicky to the bris.
他们忙着照顾家人和朋友 还有切除包皮
They'll be so busy with the family and friends,
and cutting of penises.
他们不会忘记自己邀请了他 韦斯
They're not going to forget they invited him, Wes.
我知道了 我的朋友 琼斯 他在一个在线讣告社工作
I got it. My boy Jonesy.
He works for one of those online obituaries.
我们可以杀死斯坦尼奇
We could kill Stanicky off.
我觉得可以 我们杀了他
I like that. Let's kill his ass.
把手放下 笨蛋 发布讣告需要详细信息
Put your hands down, shit nuts.
Obituaries give details. Friends, family, cemeteries.
朋友、家人、墓地
Plus then everyone's going to want to go to the funeral.
然后所有人都会想参加葬礼
Okay, Dean, your negativity is not helping.
好吧 迪恩 消极情绪没有帮助
或者我们可以按照我的原计划
Or, uh, we could go do my original plan...
告诉所有人真相
... and tell everybody the truth.
Shut your mouth. Shut your stupid mouth.
闭嘴吧 我们不会说出真相
We're not telling the truth.
没有真相可言 好吗? 我们要做正确的事
There'll be no truth told, okay?
We're going to do the right thing here.
Some would argue that telling the truth
说出真相才是正确的事
is the right thing to do.
是的 混蛋
Yeah - assholes!
让我提醒你一下真相是 梦中情奶
Let me remind you guys of what the truth is, dream cream.
昨晚 我偷偷在 马克雷比莱音乐会上狂欢时
Last night, when I was in New Jersey
secretly partying my face off at the Marc Rebillet concert,
我的妻子生下了我儿子 独自一人 好吗?
my wife was giving birth to my son.
Alone! Okay?
要是真相大白 我的婚姻也就结束了
And if the truth does come out, my marriage is over.
以后 如果我的儿子发现了 那父子之情也将断绝
And later, if my son finds out, that's over too.
Is that what you want, Wes?
那就是你想要的吗 韦斯? 你想摧毁一整个家庭吗?是吗?
You want to destroy an entire family, huh? Huh?
嘿 等等
- Huh? - Hey, hey, hey, wait a minute.
如果我们请演员扮演斯坦尼奇呢?
What if we hire an actor to play Stanicky?
We give him the whole run-down.
我们把所有情况都告诉他 告诉他他所需要知道的一切
Tell him everything he needs to know.
好的 这方法不错 继续说
Okay, okay, I like this. Keep going.
We could give him the bible, right?
我们可以把圣经给他 对吧?
He studies it for a few days,
他研究几天
然后来参加割礼几个小时
and then he comes to the bris for a couple of hours
扮演瑞奇斯坦尼奇
and he plays Ricky Stanicky.
好的 但我们上哪儿去找演员?
Okay, but where are we going to find an actor?
加里波利斯纳? 他出演了红罗宾的广告
Gary Polisner! He's in that Red Robin commercial.
- He is? - Yeah.
- 是吗? - 是的
就是他说的 “再来一份牛排薯条吗?好”
He's that dude that goes, "Seconds on steak fries?
"Uh, yeah!"
- 那是加里? - 是加里
- That's Gary? - That's Gary.
- 真好 我喜欢那些广告 - 真好 没错
- Good for him! - Good for him.
I love those commercials.
各位 有个小问题 加里正在和艾琳的表妹卡莉约会
Guys, minor wrinkle -
Gary's dating Carly, Erin's cousin.
小表妹?那个头发长得 垂到地板的女孩吗?
Oh, Cousin It?
That girl with the hair that touches the floor?
是的 但别担心
Yeah, but don't worry.
I know an actor that nobody knows.
我认识一个无人知晓的演员
罗德莱梅斯特德 训练有素的演员
老虎机+沼泽
硬摇滚罗德
♪ Grab that stick ♪
抓住那根“棍” 唾液润滑手
♪ Lube your hand with spit ♪
仰面躺下来 是时候“出击”
♪ Lay down on your back ♪
♪ Now it's time to whack ♪
勃起来临时 必须要抓住
♪ When a boner comes along You must grip it ♪
奶油流出洞 只需释放出
♪ To make the cream Come out your dong ♪
♪ Just unzip it... ♪
♪ Spoooge out my penis ♪
射出我小弟
♪ Spoooge on my tummy... ♪
射在我肚脐
♪ It's a nice day for some ♪
今日是打飞机的好时候
♪ Wood whackin' ♪
今日是再次射精的好时候
♪ It's a nice day to ♪
♪ Jizz again... ♪
♪ Ooh, baby, I masturbate ♪
哦 宝贝 我每天打飞机
♪ Every day ♪
♪ I want to tell you I masturbate every way ♪
我想告诉你 我用每种方式打飞机
我想日日夜夜打飞机
♪ Want to beat my meat Night and day ♪
耶
♪ Ay, yeah... ♪
女士们先生们 感谢今晚的到来
Thanks for coming out tonight, ladies and gentlemen.
So horny to be here. So horny to be here.
来这里太饥渴了
Great show, Rod.
- 精彩的表演 罗德 - 好观众
Good crowd.
Hey, Rod. Those guys are out there again.
嘿 罗德 那些家伙又来了
Hey, we need more beer mugs.
我们需要更多啤酒瓶
Rod Rimestead, trained actor. How can I help you?
罗德莱姆斯特德 训练有素的演员 有什么我能帮你的吗?
嗯 迪恩 我记得你
Yeah, Dean, I remember you.
工作?
A gig?
Let me... Er, you know what? Let me just check my schedule.
让我看看我的日程安排
嗯 伙计 看来我有空
Yeah, man. Looks like I'm free.
And so our feathered friend
六天前 东格林威治的 多米尼克迪帕斯奎尔医生
still has not gotten off the golf ball
把高尔夫球打到了绿地沙坑附近 而我们的羽毛朋友蹲到球上
that Dr. Dominic DiPasquale of East Greenwich
hit near this greenside bunker six days ago.
至今还没下来
但你可以相信第六频道 会一直跟踪报道这个激动人心的故事
But you can count on Channel 6 to be here
until this exciting saga ends.
或者你可以访问第六频道官网 登录到我们的实时鸭子直播
Or, you can go to Channel6.com and log onto our live duck-cam.
你能相信我为了这种垃圾内容 在新闻学院读了三年研究生吗?
Can you believe I spent three years
in journalism grad school for this crap?
你在开玩笑吗? 我很喜欢这个报道 很有趣
Are you kidding? I love this story. It's fun.
别恭维我
Don't patronize me.
好吧 这很糟 我都替你感到尴尬
Okay. It sucks. I'm embarrassed for you.
Thank you.
谢谢 你能跟我一起出来 真是太好了
You're really sweet to hang out with me, though, honestly.
- 真的 谢谢 - 你在开玩笑吗?
- Are you kidding? - Thank you.
还有谁会有机会来见证历史?
Who else gets the chance to watch history unfold?
等等 你知道还有谁在期待 明天跟瑞奇见面吗?
Oh, wait.
You know who's looking forward to meeting Ricky tomorrow?
利昂娜 我知道
Yeah, Leona. I know.
Uh-uh. Carly.
卡莉
- 卡莉 长头发那个? - 我的表妹 没错
Carly with the hair?
Mm-hm, my cousin, yeah.
加里波利斯纳怎么了?
What happened to Gary Polisner?
他们在一起了
Oh, you know, they're together,
但她在照片墙关注了瑞奇 她很喜欢他的慈善工作
but she follows Ricky on Instagram.
- Loves his charity work. - Hmm.
That duck's not going anywhere.
那只鸭子哪儿也不会去
我们去吃午饭吧 一小时后回来
Let's go get some lunch. Come back in an hour.
我很想去 但不行 我还得再等鸭子四个小时
I would, but I can't. I'm on duck duty for four more hours.
除非它起来 否则我就得困在这里了
Unless she gets up, I'm stuck here.
除非它起来 是吗?
Unless she gets up, huh.
No! Paul!
不 保罗!
Paul! Paul, come back here.
保罗 回来
嘿 保罗 回这里来
Hey, Paul. Paul, get back here.
- Paul! - Oh, my God!
- 保罗! - 天啊!
Paul!
不!保罗
-  -
天啊!快点 保罗!
Oh, my God!
Come on! Paul!
- 保罗 离开水里!反击吧 保罗 - 屏住呼吸
Paul! Get out of there!
Hold your breath, Paul!
坚持住 伙计 反击
Hang in there, buddy!
- Bad duck! - Ow!
天啊!迪恩 做点什么 你必须把它从水里拉出来!
Dean, do something! You have to pull him out of there.
保罗!
Let's take a rain check on the lunch, all right?
我们改日再约午餐吧 好吗?对不起
Sorry.
Such an asshole!
真是个混蛋
罗德岛TF格林国际机场
我只想正式声明 这是一个糟糕的主意
I just want to go on the record and say
this is a really bad idea.
为什么?他模仿名人
Why? He does impersonations of famous people.
模仿一个素未谋面的人能有多难?
How hard could it be to impersonate someone
- that no one's ever met before? - Yeah.
是啊 我们会没事的
We're going to be fine. This is going to be totally fine.
这会没事的 你把圣经给他了吧?
- You gave him the bible, right? -  Yeah.
- 是的 还有斯坦尼奇的手机 - 很好
- Good. - And the Stanicky phone,
所有信息都在上面 他的照片墙 我跟他打过视频电话
everything on it, his Insta.
I FaceTimed him. I took him through everything, man.
我跟他仔细解释了所有细节
For a sloppy drunk, he's a real pro
对于一个酒鬼而言 他在这方面可真是专家
- when it comes to this stuff. - Fine.
好吧
Oh, Jesus.
天啊
Please don't be the trash bag,
拜托 千万不要是拿那个垃圾袋
please don't be the trash bag...
是垃圾袋 不
It's the trash bag. Oh.
- 兄弟 - 什么鬼?
- Dude. - What the hell?
- 各位好啊 - 你嗑什么药了?
- Hey, boys. - What are you on?
Huh?
别骗我 你嗑什么药了?
Don't give me that shit. What drugs are you on?
None.
没嗑
别跟我们撒谎 你像一个嗑了药的人一样汗流浃背
Don't lie to us. You're sweating like a tweaker.
I'm sweating because I'm not on anything.
我出汗是因为我什么都没嗑
我已经戒了三天酒了
I've been cold-turkeying the booze for three days.
Smashes my world record by three days.
三天打破了我的纪录
什么?你现在不能戒酒 我们需要你保持最佳状态
What? You can't quit drinking right now, man.
We need you in top form!
我不能喝酒 瑞奇斯坦尼奇 参加了戒酒小组 记得吗?
I can't drink. Ricky Stanicky's in the program, remember?
哦 对哦 瑞奇改过自新了 过去七年滴酒未沾
Right, yeah, yeah.
Ricky's been clean and sober for the past seven years.
Who cares?! People relapse all the time.
谁在乎呢?人们总是好了伤疤忘了痛
-  Yeah. -  What are you...?
- 是啊 - 你在...
What are you doing?
- 你在干什么? - 钱包 嘴
Wallet. Mouth.
Oh, oh, oh!
把它放在...对
Yeah, I've seen this on 'Intervention'.
我在《勒戒》里面见过 他这是戒断反应
He's having withdrawals.
皮革会让他冷静 放松 没事的
The leather will calm him down.
- Relax. It's okay. - Yeah.
是的
You okay?
你还好吗?
我在飞机上出现了几次这种情况 都熬过来了
I had a couple of those in the plane - they pass.
和我一起下飞机的那个好人 他帮助了我
The nice fella I walked off the plane with, he helped me.
什么人?
What fella?
他刚刚在这里 你们没看见他吗?
He was just... he was just here. You didn't see him?
卷曲的眼睛、金色的长嘴唇 他说话时跛脚
Curly eyes. Long blonde lips. He talks with a limp.
All right, uh,
我们就闻一下伏特加的味道怎么样?
how about we just take a little whiff of vodka,
就稍微减轻一点戒断反应 好吗?
you know, just to take the edge off?
- Yeah. A little bit. - Yeah?
- 嗯 一点 - 不行
No, you hired me to play the role of a sober gentleman.
你们雇我来扮演一个不喝酒的绅士
I'm going to do so the only way I know how -
我会秉持着艺术诚信做到这一点
with artistic integrity.
那是什么?有人在煮龙虾吗?
What is that? Is somebody boiling lobster?
煮什么?
Boiling what? Oh, Rod.
罗德...
- Oh. -
It's not what you think it is.
不是你们想的那样 这只是小便
It's just piss.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
不敢相信你们竟然开这车来接我
I can't believe you guys picked me up in this thing.
什么?
What?
这耗油的碳排放地球杀手
This gas-guzzling, carbon-emitting Earth-killer.
你们的家人看见我坐在这车里 我肯定就露馅了
If your people see me pull up in this thing,
my cover is blown for sure.
他又说对了 瑞奇斯坦尼奇是一个环保人士
He's right again. Ricky Stanicky's a tree hugger.
我们帮他清理了 切萨皮克湾 记得吗?
We helped him clean up the Chesapeake Bay, remember?
爱国者和乌鸦队的比赛 那场比赛很精彩
The Pats/Ravens game. That was a good game.
- 那是谁? - 没谁
-  Who's that? - Nobody.
好的 庄家是谁?
All right, who's the bank? I want all my cheese up front.
我希望所有费用事先结清 符合工会最低标准
SAG minimum - $983 a day, meal penalty after six hours.
一天983美元 超过六小时要提供餐食
兄弟 你肯定没加入工会
Dude, there is no way you're in the union.
We'll give you half now and half when you're done.
现在支付一半 演完后一半
- 这可不好 我要求预付 - 没有商量的余地
That's a no-bueno. I want all my cake up front.
It's not negotiable.
好的 那好吧
Okay, then, that's a bueno.
Guys, we can't take him to the bris smelling like this.
他这味道 我们不能带他参加割礼
Wes, can you please take Mr. Stanicky
韦斯 你能带斯坦尼奇先生去你家
over to your place and shower him off
让他洗个澡 再带他去JT家吗?
and then bring him over to JT's?
是瑞奇 斯坦尼奇先生 是我假爸爸的名字
It's 'Ricky'. Mr. Stanicky is my fake father's name.
Um, hey, I don't think that's going to be a good idea.
嘿 我觉得这不是一个好主意
- 我的浴帘都发霉了 - 别再推脱了
My shower curtains, they're all mouldy and shit.
Wes, stop being a douchebag.
Erin and I have to get there early and help set up.
艾琳和我必须帮他们布置现场 我们会比你先到
So we're going to be there way before you. Just...
我不知道 尽力而为吧 给他打扮得体 拜托
I don't know, do what you can, make him presentable, please.
得体?你怎么敢这么说?
Presentable? How dare you.
You guys are supposed to be my best friends.
作为我最好的朋友 你们应该争相让我变干净
You should be fighting over who gets to hose me down.
嘿 尿裤子奶奶 闭嘴 好吗?
Hey, grand-mal piss-pants. Shut the fuck up, okay?
如果你闻起来
We wouldn't be in this predicament
不像疗养院里的床垫一样 我们也不至于这样
if you didn't show up smelling like a nursing-home mattress.
Wow. This is a hostile set.
这真是一个充满敌意的组合
非常感谢 我开始感觉好点了
Thanks for that, man.
Starting to feel a little human again.
嗯 我问你一件事
Yeah. Hey, let me ask you something.
You're a raging alcoholic, right?
- 你是个酗酒狂 对吗? - 是的
Yeah.
Well, then how do you stay so ripped?
那你是怎么保持肌肉的?
- Roids. Shit-ton of roids. - Hmm.
合成类固醇 大量的合成类固醇
我也对合成类固醇上瘾
I got addicted to those too.
God, they're good.
天啊 那可是好东西
Wow. Gay much?
- 同性伴侣? - 对
Yeah. I was really feeling it that day.
那天我真的很有感觉
- 这是你的... - 伴侣 基思
Oh, so this is your, um...
Partner, Keith. Mmm.
是的
Of course.
顺便一提 我跟他说你是双性恋
By the way, I kind of told him that you were bi.
什么?为什么?
What? Why?
因为我们约过会 如果你不是双性恋会很奇怪
Because it'd be weird if you weren't...
since we dated.
我们约过会?你和我? 圣经里有这段记录吗?
We dated? You and me? Was that in the bible?
- 我没看到那段 - 没 没在圣经里
- I missed that. - No, it's not in there.
为什么这条信息不在圣经里?
Why the hell wasn't it in the bible?
Well, 'cause I couldn't tell the guys. All right?
因为我不能告诉他们俩 好吗?
我当时不知道我和基思的 第一次约会会如何发展
Look, look, I didn't know how things would go
on my first date with Keith.
所以我跟他说 我要去见一个名叫瑞奇斯坦尼奇的人
So I told him I was seeing this dude named Ricky Stanicky,
以防万一我需要脱身
in case I needed an out.
But we hit it off and I told him we broke up.
但我们一拍即合 我就跟他说我们分手了
好的 没问题
Okay, no problem.
不幸的是 基思仍然视你为威胁
Unfortunately, Keith's still a little threatened by you.
好吧 全盘托出吧 我需要知道一切
Okay, spill the beans. I got to know everything.
- What did you tell him we did? - What do you mean?
- 你跟他说我们做过些什么? - 什么意思?
Cut the crap. You know what I mean.
废话少说 你知道我的意思
我们玩小熊维尼找蜂蜜棒了吗?
Did we play Winnie the Pooh finds a honey stick?
- What's that? - Munchkins in a cave?
- 那是什么? - 小人儿进山洞呢?
Upside-down barber?
倒立理发师?剃饼干和肉汁呢?
Shaved biscuits and gravy?
- 不 没! - 颜射?
- No. - Old faceful?
No! We just went on a couple of dates.
我们只是约会了几次
Oh. I guess I didn't do it for you.
我猜我没替你做那些事
也不值得为你做那些 猎犬耳朵
You're no trophy either, beagle ears.
这是什么?
Hey, what's this?
这只是...
Oh, it's just this... this children's book thing
这是我一直在修改的儿童读物
that I've been tinkering with.
Hey, there he is! Our mohel, Rabbi Greenberg.
他来了!这是我们的 割礼执行人拉比格林伯格
你可以叫我拉比笑笑鸟
You can call me Rabbi Gigglebird.
拉比有时在喜剧中心表演单口相声
The Rabbi does stand-up sometimes
at the Comedy Connection.
我可能吃不了火腿 但我可以成为“火腿”
I may not be able to eat ham, but I can certainly be one!
Cheese puffs, anyone?
有人要吃奶酪泡芙吗?
Oh, no, we mohels, we prefer those little weenies.
不 我们割礼执行人 更喜欢那些小鸡鸡
吧嗒砰!
Ba-doomp-pow!
好家伙
Oh, no...
Listen. Listen.
听着 我今天的服务是免费的
My services here today are complimentary,
just so you know, all right?
只是让你知道 好吗?
I consider this a mitzvah. All right?
我认为这是善行 好吗?
我不想要钱 但我会留着小费
I don't want any money,
but I'm keeping the tip!
- They just keep on coming, huh? - Yeah, they don't stop.
- 真是段子不断啊 - 对 源源不断
- All right. - You're hungry, I bet.
- 你肯定饿了吧 - 一直很饿
Always.
Please. You got to fill up before you... Right?
请吧 你得先填饱肚子再... 好吗?去吧 都是你的
- Go. It's all you, baby. - Yeah, yeah. Go get it. Dig in.
好 去吧 去吃吧
别碰那个巴布卡蛋糕 女士
Back off the vodka, lady.
天啊!
Oh, Jesus Christ.
我能喝一杯金汤力吗?要双份酒的
Can I get a gin and tonic? And let's make it a double.
- 萨默海耶斯在这里做什么? - 我邀请了他
What the fuck is Summerhayes doing here?
I invited him.
- Oh, my God. - Babe, why would you do that?
- 天啊 - 宝贝 你为什么要邀请他?
Because he's your boss.
因为他是你的老板
对 我不想跟我的老板玩
Yeah. I don't want to hang out with my boss.
为什么啊?迎婴派对的时候 你邀请了他啊 混蛋
Why not? You invited him to the baby shower, shithead.
That's different. This is a cock-cutting ceremony.
那不一样
这是割小弟弟仪式 我不希望他在场
I don't want him here.
Jesus Christ, you're being weird. Just go say hi.
你真奇怪 去打个招呼吧 你们俩都去 快去
Both of you. Go.
Great. This is just great.
太好了 这太棒了
现在 要是斯坦尼奇搞砸了 我们都会失去工作
Now if Stanicky shits the bed, we lose our jobs.
God, where is he? He should be here by now.
他在哪儿?他现在应该已经到了
Explain it again.
再解释一次
这个儿童故事的主角 是这些在微风中飞舞的种子
It's a children's story about these seeds
that are flying in the breeze,
它们想要做的就是到达山顶
and all they want to do is reach the top of this mountain.
But there's this one little seed who gets blown back
但有一颗小种子
被吹回了山脚
to the bottom of the mountain,
它就说:“去你妈!”
and she's all like, "Fuck!"
但当开始下雨时
But when it starts to rain, all the water will start
所有的水会沿着山的一侧直接流向它
to flow down the side of the mountain straight to her.
So she'll sprout and she'll grow and grow
所以它会发芽、成长 长成树木中最大的一棵
to be the biggest tree of all,
甚至比山顶的那些树都大
even bigger than the ones on top of the mountain.
要传达的信息是
The message being,
无论你出身如何 你都能在生活中成就伟业
you can be great in life, no matter where you start.
太垃圾了
Hot, wet shit.
等等 你在说什么?
What-what... what are you talking about?
拜托 伙计 你不是农民 你到底对种子了解些什么?
Come on, man, you're not a farmer.
What the hell do you know about seeds, right?
传递的信息很荒谬
And the message is absurd.
Poor kids turn into trees? It doesn't make any sense.
可怜的孩子变成大树 这根本说不通
- 你说得对 这很蠢 - 是吧?
- You're right. - Right?
It is stupid. It's stupid!
很蠢 我到底在想什么啊 兄弟?
What the fuck was I thinking, man? Yeah.
是啊 我应该放弃
I should just give up.
不 我没说你该放弃
Whoa. No. That's not what I said.
我说这个故事很垃圾 因为它不够真实
I said this is crap,
because it's not authentic.
Doesn't mean you gotta give up.
这并不意味着你该放弃
我给你讲个故事吧 牛仔
Let me tell you a story, cowboy.
A few years back,
几年前 我在游艇上 主持过一场限制级狗狗表演
I had an X-rated dog show at the Showboat.
我有两只杂种狗 它们能用传教士式交配
I had these two mutts that could bang missionary style.
嗯 你没听错 传教士 面对面 “真枪实弹”
Oh, yeah, you heard me right. Missionary!
Face-to-face. Real deal.
其实挺感人的
It was kind of touching, actually.
然后大西洋城的人都“觉醒”了 不允许它们上台表演
Then Atlantic City gets all woke
and they won't let 'em pump on stage anymore.
我试着和两个穿狗狗衣服的人 完成这个节目
I tried doing the show with two guys in dog suits, but...
但效果很不好 你明白我的意思吗?
the magic just wasn't there.
You know what I mean?
不明白
- No. - My point is, I failed.
我的意思是 我失败了 但我放弃了吗?当然没有
But did I give up? Heck no.
我决定扪心自问 我爱什么? 然后就很容易了
I just had to ask myself, what do I love?
And then it was easy -
唱歌、表演以及讲黄段子
singing, performing and telling filthy jokes.
And that is when Rock Hard Rod was born.
就在那时 硬摇滚罗德诞生了
而你 先生
You, sir, have just found out
刚发现自己的狗不能 再表演传教士式交配
your dogs can no longer bang missionary style.
现在 你得问自己 你爱什么?
Now you got to ask yourself, what do you love?
- What do I love? - Yeah.
- 我爱什么? - 对
Ah...
我想想
Yeah, I... I like ceramic owls?
嗯 我喜欢陶瓷猫头鹰 青蛙
Uh... I love fog.
我喜欢青蛙 很喜欢
I love fog! I love it.
你喜欢的事物里
Er, is there anything that you like
有没有任何 能与普通人产生共鸣的呢?
that a regular human being can relate to on any level?
- I like Christmas. - Christmas, Christmas!
- 我喜欢圣诞节 - 圣诞节 很完美!
Perfect! Yes! Everybody loves Christmas.
- 很好 - 大家都爱圣诞节
对 好吧 并不是每个人都喜欢 基思最近就不太喜欢圣诞节
Yeah, well, not everybody.
Keith is not a big fan of it these days.
- 他不喜欢圣诞节? - 他以前喜欢 但是...
- He doesn't love Christmas? - Well, he used to love it.
But, I mean,
自从他父母发现我们在约会以后
ever since his parents found out that we were dating,
他们就没再邀请他圣诞回去
they haven't really invited him over.
那太糟了
- That sucks. - Yeah.
是的 这是他们的损失 他们不能吃“月度俱乐部肉干”了
Which is their loss, you know.
No "Jerky of the Month Club" for them.
Ha.
I just wish there was a holiday tradition for us.
我只是希望我们能有节日传统
You know, like Christmas is the gayest holiday anyway, man.
总之 圣诞节是最欢乐的节日
You know, you bedazzle a tree with tinsel.
你用金属丝装饰一棵树
And why does Santa have to be such a fat shit?
圣诞老人为什么一定要这么胖?
他不能有肌肉吗?不能肌肉发达吗?
Couldn't he be ripped? Couldn't he be jacked? You know?
难道精灵们不能给他买个动感单车 或者瑜伽垫之类的吗?
Can the elves have ordered him a Peloton
or a yoga mat or something?
这就对了 这就很真实
Ra-pum-pum-pum.
Now that is authentic!
对 我们的圣诞故事
Yeah. A Christmas story for us.
Thanks for coming, Ted.
谢谢你过来 特德
我知道你不喜欢割礼
I know a bris isn't exactly your cup of tea.
不 我们很高兴你邀请了我们 JT
Oh, no, we're happy that you invited us, JT.
这正是特德需要的
This is exactly what Ted needed.
他痴迷于他的世界河流公司的合并案
He's been so obsessed with this World River merger.
对
Yeah.
Circumcision parties are my go-to when I need to relax.
我需要放松的时候 就喜欢参加割礼派对
加里在哪里?我以为他会来
Where's Gary? I thought he was coming.
He has his improv class at Trinity,
他在三一学院上即兴表演课 但他很快就会过来
but I think he'll be here soon.
- 你们看了他的新广告吗? - 看了
Have you guys seen his new commercial?
Yeah. Yeah.
它下来了
- He got off. - Who got off?
谁下来了?
My big story I'm covering this week.
- 我这周报道的大新闻 - 你在报道庭审吗?
You're covering a trial?
没 真正的记者才会报道那种事
No, real reporters get to do that.
我在报道万纳莫伊赛特乡村俱乐部
I'm covering a vicious duck sitting on a golf ball
- 一只坐在高尔夫球上的凶猛鸭子 - 你的辛苦会有回报的 好吗?
- at Wannamoisett Country Club. - Oh.
You're just paying your dues, right?
你很快就会有机会报道大新闻的
You're going to get a shot at the big story soon.
- 谢谢你 宝贝 - 他不会来了 对吗?
Thanks, babe.
He's not coming, is he?
- Who would you be referring to? - Oh, don't give me that.
- 你说的是谁? - 别装傻
Ricky Stanicky. Where the hell is he?
瑞奇斯坦尼奇 他到底在哪里?
他会来的 瑞奇就这样 他...他总是迟到
Oh, he'll be here. This is just typical Ricky.
He's... he's always late.
Hmm. Well, I'll believe it when I see it.
好吧 眼见为实
利昂娜 拜托 他怎么会不来呢?
Leona, come on. Why wouldn't he come?
可能跟他不愿意
Probably for the same reason
出席JT和苏珊的婚礼的原因一样
that he didn't bother to show up for JT and Susan's wedding.
很抱歉他觉得我的婚礼
Sorry he didn't think my wedding was more important
than digging out hurricane victims in the Bahamas.
不如挖掘巴哈马的飓风受害者重要
Ooh.
Ha, ha! The old Bahamian hurricane.
以前的那次巴哈马飓风
Jackie, tell me about Ricky Stanicky.
杰基 跟我说说这个瑞奇斯坦尼奇
既然他们是这么铁的朋友
I mean, if they were such good friends,
他们小时候 你一定见过他很多次吧?
you must have met him a bunch when they were kids, right?
Oh, sure. I... I met all of JT's friends.
- 当然了 我见过JT所有的朋友 - 真的吗?
Really?
你对他有什么特别的记忆吗?
Do you have any specific memories of him?
我记得他是个刺头 这是肯定的
Well, I remember he was a handful, that's for sure.
I mean, every time this one got in trouble,
每次这个人遇到麻烦时 斯坦尼奇肯定是幕后黑手
Stanicky was somehow behind it.
He was a... a little devil, that Ricky.
- 那个瑞奇是个小恶魔 - 是啊
- Yeah. Oh, yeah. - Wow!
那听起来跟在非洲
That doesn't sound like the same guy
为博诺工作并在秘鲁 建立孤儿院的不像是一个人
who works for Bono in Africa and builds orphanages in Peru.
那是因为他重生了
That's 'cause he's born again.
- Ah. - He had that epiphany in rehab.
他在康复期间顿悟 我跟你说过的
Remember I told you about that?
是啊 人是会变的 利昂娜
- Mm-hm. - Yeah, people change, Leona.
你为什么要拷问我妈妈? 她不该受审
Why are you grilling my mom? She's not on trial.
因为我想让你承认 那个瑞奇斯坦尼奇并不存在
Because I want you to admit
that Ricky Stanicky does not exist.
Hey, mishpocha!
嘿 家人们
Let's get down to bris-ness!
我们开始割礼吧!
- 斯坦尼奇! - 嘿!耶!好!
Oh, yes! Yeah-ah!
你来了!
You made it!
The boys are back!
男孩们回来了
- 好的 - 杰基!
- All right. - Jackie!
Ricky?
瑞奇?
Oh, you look unbelievable. You're still a MILF.
您真是太惊人了 还那么性感
Oh, my God.
天啊 看看你 你一点都没变
Look at you. Oh, you haven't changed a bit.
那个神秘人的真身
The mystery man in the flesh.
好吧 你还真是性感得令人心动
Well, churn my butter with a slippery stick.
我终于见到艾琳哈福德了 你本人比迪恩
I finally get to meet Erin Harford.
You're even more beautiful in person
总给我发的照片里好看
than the pictures Dean's always sending me.
You send him pictures of me?
- 你给他发过我的照片? - 当然很有品味
Oh, tasteful, of course.
Even the nudes.
甚至是裸体的时候
Seriously, the guy doesn't shut up about you.
这家伙总是说你的事 上周你说她什么来着?
What were you saying about her last week?
It was, um...
说...
Ah! The more I look at her,
“我越看她
“就越觉得有看头”
the more I realize how much there is to see.
- Aw. Babe. - And who do we have here?
宝贝
这位是谁 长发公主 放下你的头发!
Rapunzel, Rapunzel, let down your hair!
我是卡莉 艾琳的表妹
I'm Carly, I'm Erin's cousin.
久仰大名 无需介绍!
No need to shout, bullhorn!
而我就是那个独自一人生产的女人
And I am the woman who had to give birth all alone
因为你骗了我的丈夫 让他去了奥尔巴尼
because you tricked her husband into going to Albany.
Oh, my God, Susan, I'm so sorry.
天啊 苏珊 非常抱歉
You know how much grief your old man's been giving me?
你男人狠狠批评了我
For the record, I had no idea it was your baby shower.
我不知道那是你的宝宝的迎婴派对
I just wanted to celebrate my new lease on life
我当时想跟我最好的朋友们 一起庆祝我的新生
with my oldest, dearest friends.
而小惠特克出生了 天 我爱死这个名字了
Then little Whitaker comes along...
God, I love that name.
And then I just ruin everything.
然后 我就搞砸了一切
我就...我再次致以最诚挚的歉意
I just... Again, my sincerest apologies.
No, you know, it...
不...没事 我知道 你经历了很多事情 所以...
It's okay. I know you've been through a lot, so...
Hell, yeah, they lopped off one of my nuts, for starters.
是啊 一开始 医生切掉了我的一个蛋蛋
-  - Oh, you are still a handful!
你还是刺头!
半个刺头吧
Well, half a handful.
-  - Ricky...
- 瑞奇... - 好吧 阿里 嘿
Okay, Rico! Hey, let's go show you around. Huh?
我们带你四处看看吧
Aren't you going to Introduce me?
- 你不准备介绍我吗? - 我们马上回来
Uh, we'll be right back.
Stay away from that woman at all costs, okay?
不惜一切代价远离那个女人 她是苏珊的妈妈 非常难搞
That's Susan's mother. She's bad news.
好的
天啊
Jesus.
嘿 如果有人问起手抖的事 就说
Hey, if anyone asks about the shaking, just say,
“我有低血糖 还喝了红牛”
"I have low blood sugar and I had a Red Bull."
打住 我不喜欢照搬台词
Stopping you there.
I don't appreciate line readings.
What?
什么?
所以我掀起了蚊帐
So, I lift up the mosquito net
果然 博诺就在那里 像耕土豆田一样“耕”博诺夫人
and, sure enough, Bono's in there.
Plowing Mrs. Bono like a potato field.
真的吗?那个博诺?
Really? The Bono?
是啊 把古老的爱尔兰战棍 塞给他的太太
Yeah. Givin' the missus the old Irish shillelagh, as it were.
所以我尴尬地站在那里 然后他们说 “看吧 我们喜欢人看”
So I'm standing there embarrassed.
And then they go,  "It's okay.
"Watch us, we like it."
这就是爱尔兰特色吗?
Is that an Irish thing?
我觉得不是 但我相信他们干得出来
I don't think so. But I wouldn't put it past them.
这家伙让一千万人免于挨饿
Hey, the guy saved ten million people from starving.
所以如果他想让人看他 “料理”他妻子的“卷心菜”
So, if he wants to let people
watch him corn-beef his wife's cabbage, who am I to stop him?
我有什么理由阻止他呢?
你知道城市里 最好料理师是谁吗?是杰夫
You know who has the best corn-beef in town? Geoff's.
那甚至不是真正的熟食店
And it isn't even really a deli.
我觉得他口中的“料理” 可能不是一回事 金妮
I don't think that's the kind of corn-beef
he's talking about, Ginny.
说这些食物让我都饿了 你吃了吗?
Oh, man, all this food talk is making me hungry.
- Ricky, have you eaten yet? -  Dean.
迪恩 你还没把我 介绍给这位“印第安纳琼斯”认识呢
You haven't introduced me to Indiana Jones here.
好的
Yeah, of course.
特德 这位是我的好朋友 瑞奇斯坦尼奇
Ted, this is Ricky Stanicky, my good friend.
瑞奇 这是特德萨默海耶斯 我老板
Uh, Ricky, this is Ted Summerhayes, my boss.
Ted, nice to meet you.
特德 幸会 我很喜欢你的头发毛和衣服
Digging the suit and the seedlings, man.
The seedlings?
头发毛?
The hair plugs. They're new, right?
发片 是新的 对吧?
What?
什么?不 这是我的头发
No. This is my hair.
是啊 就跟洋娃娃的头发 是她的头发一样 好好笑
Ha! Yeah, just like a doll's hair is her hair.
That's good. That's good.
所以 特德 你是大银行家 对吧?
So, Ted, you're one of those big banker guys, eh?
One of those guys out there
那种帮助亿万富翁变得更富有的人
helping those billionaires get richer
然后坐在巨大而摇摆的游艇上 在水面漂浮
and then floating around on your big swinging super-yachts,
leaving everybody else struggling to make ends meet
让其他所有人努力维持收支平衡
in their little dinghies.
- 不 不是 - 首先...
- No. No, no, no. Not at all... - First of all,
we sell financial services to independent investors,
我们向独立投资者提供金融服务
其次 任何愿意为此服务付费的人 都可分享利益
and anyone who's willing to pay for them
is welcome to share in the benefits.
你怎么安心怎么想呗 埃比尼泽
Whatever helps you sleep at night, Ebenezer.
Uh, if memory serves me,
我没记错的话 埃比尼泽斯克鲁奇 最后成了那本小说的英雄
Ebenezer Scrooge ends up
becoming the hero of that story.
- 是瑞奇 对吧? - 对
- It's Ricky, right? -  Yeah.
我想知道 瑞奇
I'm wondering, Ricky, are you always such a bust-out asshole,
你一直都这么讨人厌吗?
right out of the gate?
Only when I'm talking to the type of guy
只有当我跟足以改变这个世界的人 聊天的时候 我才会这样
who can make a real difference in this world.
Ted, Ricky's been working overseas
特德 过去十年 瑞奇一直 在海外从事非营利组织工作
for the last decade on non-profits.
所以至少他说到做到
So at least he walks the walk.
那很不错
Well, that's nice,
但他显然是从《赫芬顿邮报》
but he's obviously getting his financial information
获取的财务信息
from 'The Huffington Post'.
No, actually, I've been reading
不 我最近一直在看 《旧金山纪事报》
the 'San Francisco Chronicle' lately.
你跟世界河流公司的潜在合并交易
I've been following
your potential merger with World River.
很有趣 很意外
It's interesting, unexpected.
好了 里面还有很多人想见见你呢...
Okay, hey, uh, there's a ton of people inside
- that still wanna meet you. - Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'd like to hear this.
我想听他说完 怎么意外了?
Unexpected, how?
Oh, come on.
拜托 他们是阴 而你们是老公司 是阳
They're the yin, and you got that big old yang.
我的意思是 那样很搭
It's a perfect fit.
In what way?
怎么很搭了?
你们公司是老派作风 他们是新时代
Well, you're old school. They're new age.
你有常识 但他们有激进的新想法
You got common sense, but they got radical new ideas.
为了我的钱 我会一直遵循常识 而不管激进的新想法
For my money, I'm going common sense
over radical new ideas all day.
波特兰和旧金山的人都会同意
I'm sure the people in Portland and San Francisco agree.
而这就是你们的伟大之处 但他们也很不错
And that's what makes you guys great.
But they're pretty good too.
你们联手 将势不可挡
But, together, you guys would be unstoppable.
这次合并可能会改变世界格局 特德
This merger could make a real difference in this world, Ted.
造成真正的影响
A real difference.
就像阴阳结合 对吗?
Yin and yang, huh?
Oh, don't mind if I do. Thanks.
不介意的话 我要拿走这个 谢谢
你到底是从哪里 打听到世界河流交易的事的?
Where the hell did you hear about the World River deal?
They were all over your Twitter.
你的推特上面写的 我稍微研究了一下
I just did a little research.
- 你在我的推特上做什么? - 迪恩 我说过 我是一名演员
What are you doing on my Twitter?
Dean, I told you I'm an actor.
When I walk into a room,
我走进这间屋子时 我想知道自己要面对什么
I want to know exactly where I came from
我想知道屋子里每个人都在做什么
and what every single person in that room's been doing.
That's what all the greats do.
这就是所有佼佼者会做的事
Matt Damon actually bought a zoo
马特达蒙在拍《我家买了动物园》前 买下了一座动物园
before he filmed 'We Bought a Zoo'.
I don't think that's true.
我觉得那是假消息
You don't believe me? Take it up with Reddit.
你不信我吗?去Reddit了解一下
Oh, if you'll excuse me,
失陪了 我要去跟基思谈谈
I got to go have a word with Keith.
什么?你怎么认识基思的?
What? How do you know Keith?!
我们陷入了一段奇怪的三角恋之中
We're in a weird love-triangle thing.
Look, all I'm saying is I hope there's no hard feelings.
听着 我只是希望你不会生气
Because let's face it, you won.
因为我们面对事实吧 你赢了 但我为你感到高兴
But I'm happy for you.
你们是天作之合
You guys make a fabulous couple.
I'm done with his ass.
我受够那个混蛋了
听着 我还爱他
Look, I still love the guy,
但我厌倦了一周工作60个小时
but I'm tired of working 60 hours a week
而他就干坐着 不做任何事情来提高自己
while he sits around not doing anything to improve himself.
I just...
我不能再跟这样的人在一起了
I can't be with a person like that anymore.
那他的写作呢?那就是工作
What... what about his writing? That's work.
What writing?
- 什么写作? - 他正在写的书
The book he's working on.
他从没告诉我他正在写书
He never told me he was writing a book.
他看起来真的比你们老很多
He sure looks a lot older than you guys.
- Really? - Mmm.
真的吗?
是的 好吧 他要大几岁 我们就像他的小弟弟一样
Yeah, well, he is, by a couple years.
You know, we were like little brothers to him.
Hmm, no, I mean, like more than a couple of years.
不 我是说 看着可不止大几岁
Well, it's because of the drugs - he...
因为毒品
对 他以前经常参加派对
You know, he was a huge partier, back in the day.
会用烈性毒品、嗑药 做那些混账事
I mean, like hard drugs.
Huffing glue. Like, the works.
I mean, that'll suck the youth right out of your face.
- 那会让你的容颜变老 - 确实
It does.
Yeah, that was all before he went on
那都是他走上正道之前的事了
- the straight and narrow. - Hmm.
看看他们 看他们多开心啊
Oh, look at them. Look how happy they are.
-  I told you. -  It's an easy thing.
- 我没看出来他们很幸福 - 什么?
-  I don't see happiness. -  What?
I see fear and anxiety.
我看到了恐惧和焦虑
Fear of what?
害怕什么?
为人父母的责任 他们从中得到什么?
Of the responsibility of it all.
What do they even get out of it?
他们从组建家庭中得到了什么?
What do they get out of having a family?
- 是啊 - 拜托
- Yeah. - Come on.
I mean, I get it on paper. Sure, right.
理论上 我明白
但事实上 养孩子会让人恐惧而焦虑
But in reality, having a kid is fear and anxiety
有时还会让人觉得痛苦不堪
with periodic moments of crushing pain.
And then you get bitter and resentful
然后你会愤怒 会怨恨 最终就...
and eventually just... mean.
变得刻薄
至少我家就是这样
At least that's how it was at my house.
要知道这是你跟我 讲你童年的事讲得最多的一次
You realize that's the most you've ever
told me about your childhood?
Look, he is kind of lost right now,
他现在有点迷失了方向
给他一点时间 他会解决的
but just give him a little time, he'll figure it out.
我已经给了他充足的时间
I've given him plenty of time.
我觉得这需要你再次介入 瑞奇
I think you need to step back in, Ricky.
Be there for him.
陪在他身边 等我跟他分手时 安慰一下他
Ease the blow a little when I drop him.
嘿 基思 你再想想
Oh, hey, Keith, slow down.
相信我 像你们这样的关系并不常见
Take it from me, relationships like yours,
they don't come around that often.
They just don't.
我的亲生母亲结过六次婚
My own mother was married six times.
她始终没有找到幸福
She never found happiness.
An incredible sex life,
她的性生活精彩纷呈 可她内心唯一缺少的就是快乐
but she was filled up with everything but joy.
You really want to give up on this?
你真的想放弃这段感情吗? 它可能不会回来
May not come back around.
瑞奇
Ricky!
我知道你在肯尼亚待了很长时间
I understand you spent a lot of time in Kenya
跟给予绿色组织合作
working with the Give Green organization.
是的 那些人都是好人 很重视环保
Yeah, yeah, good peeps.
Green peeps, yeah.
我很感兴趣你在那里的经历
I'm interested in what your experience was there,
because, you know, I've been reading up on them
我一直在研究他们
真的是一个很有趣的组织
and they're a really intriguing organization.
Yeah, you know what?
嗯 我只是想找奶酪泡芙托盘
I was just trying to find one of those cheese-puff trays.
我带你去拿
- I'll show you where they are. - Right, but before you do,
你走之前 能告诉我查理森内特的事吗?
can you tell me about Charlie Sennet?
Huh?
- 什么? - 记者查理森内特
Charlie Sennet, the journalist who started Give Green
给予绿色组织的创始人 而且现在依然参与活动
and is still hands on.
我的意思是 你见过他吗?
I mean, did you get to meet him?
你觉得他的目标怎么样? 是否站得住脚?
What do you think of his mission statement?
Is it tenable?
Oh, yeah, of course it's tenable.
当然站得住脚了
非常、极其、无限站得住 对吧?...
Elevenable, twelveable...
I mean, it's infinite really, right?
我对他们的 直接慈善捐款政策很感兴趣
Ha-ha.
I mean, I'm intrigued by their policy
of direct charitable donations.
You know, personally, I think
就个人而言 我认为 捐款应该是有条件的
donations need to be conditional.
What do you think?
你觉得呢?
Uh, you know what?
那个 我觉得该拍集体照了
It's group photo time. Group photo time.
Group photo! Come on, let's make some memories!
- 我们去留下一些回忆吧 - 好的
Yeah. Yeah.
你不知道我在说什么 对吧?
You have no idea what I'm talking about, do you, Ricky?
也许他只是不想在割礼上 谈论工作 利昂娜
Maybe he just doesn't want to talk shop at a bris, Leona.
或者他是个骗子 你是骗子吗 先生?
Or maybe he's a fraud. Are you a fraud, sir?
I'll tell you what's fraudulent, Leona.
- 我来告诉你什么是欺骗 利昂娜 - 好啊
Yeah?
我对于给予绿色组织 需要采用有条件现金转账的看法
The perception that the program at Give Green
needs to be conditional.
他们选择提供 无条件现金转账有两个原因
They choose to offer unconditional cash transfers
for two reasons.
首先 赋予贫困人群 能够自主选择的权力
First, empowering poor people to make their own choices?
符合他们尊重的核心价值观
Well, that advances their core value of respect.
Second, imposing conditions requires
其次 施加强制条件需要
expensive monitoring and enforcement structures
昂贵的检测和执行机构
这可能会让行政成本增加高达63%
that could raise administrative costs as high as 63%.
对于有条件和无条件
The existing empirical evidence comparing the impact
现金转账影响的比较 现有实证
of conditional to unconditional cash transfers
shows that these added costs
表明这些额外成本 并没有产生相应的效益
simply do not produce commensurate benefits.
不知道那些奶酪泡芙托盘去哪儿了?
I wonder where those cheese-puff trays went off to.
你想吃奶酪泡芙吗 利昂娜?
Did you want a cheese puff, Leona?
不用了 谢谢
No, thank you.
谢谢 这是什么?
Huh, so what are these?
阿夏戈奶酪和腌制鲱鱼馅的蜜枣
Glazed dates stuffed with Asiago cheese
and pickled herring.
Don't mind if I don't.
- 别介意我放回去 - 没事
No problem.
- That was amazing. - Unbelievable.
- 太精彩了 - 难以置信
Where the hell did you learn all that stuff?
你到底是从哪里学的那些东西?
Gotta buy the zoo, baby.
得买动物园呀
What? Who's that...?
什么?那是谁...
加里波利斯纳来了
Gary Polisner's here.
$8,000. It's on lease, but that's how much it's worth.
八千美元 这是租来的
但这表价值这么多
Oh.
Hey, Polisner!
嘿 波利斯纳
Hey! Well you move along, I'll talk to you later on.
嘿
你们去玩吧 我稍后再跟你们聊
过来吧
Get over here, hey?
我不得不把我的电动皮卡停在临县
Had to park my Cybertruck in the next county.
怎么?你太抠门了 舍不得付代客泊车的钱?
What, you too cheap for a valet?
糟了 我认识那家伙
- Crap! I know that guy. - What? What guy?
什么?哪个人?
跟长发克利希娜站在一起的那个人
The guy standing with Hairy Krishna.
我给你留了一个贝果 夹的是熏鲑鱼
I saved you a bagel with lox.
我要的是什么都加的贝果 结果来了个什么都没的贝果
I asked for an everything bagel. That's a nothing bagel.
- 这地方有酒吗? - 有
Hey, you got any booze in this place?
Yeah.
让我猜猜 这是个现金酒吧
Let me guess, it's a cash bar.
Oh, shit!
糟了
上楼 去车库 直接过去吧
Go up the stairs. Go into the garage.
Just get in there. Don't come out until I tell you.
等我叫你再出来 好吗? 去吧 他妈的
All right? Go, go, go, go, go.
Fuck.
你们能看出 我其实不流汗
And as you can tell, I actually don't sweat...
你他妈说什么?
What the fuck are you saying?
瑞奇认识波利斯纳
Ricky knows Polisner.
怎么认识的?
- How? - How the hell do I know?
我怎么知道? 也许他们都是演员 打过交道
They're both actors. Maybe they crossed paths somehow.
We got to get Polisner out of here.
我们得让波利斯纳离开这里
He just got here.
他刚到
该死的
Goddamn it.
- 我们可以氯他 - 什么意思?
We could put him in a K-hole.
What's that?
就是给他服用氯胺酮麻醉药
Dose him with ketamine.
好主意 我跑去药店买一瓶
Yeah, great idea. I'll just run down to CVS and grab a bottle.
不需要
No need.
你怎么会有氯胺酮?
Why the hell do you have ketamine?
Well, sometimes after a hard day, you...
有时 辛苦了一天之后...
You K-hole yourself.
你会氯自己?
我看得出来 你从哪儿弄到这药的?
I could see that. Where do you get these things?
- My grandmother died. - Guys!
- 我祖母有... - 各位 我们不会氯任何人
We're not K-holing anyone.
Stop being such a fucking wang, Dean. Okay?
迪恩 别像个混蛋一样 好吗?
We're going to get him a little drowsy
我们会让他昏昏欲睡 然后把他送进出租车
and then put him in a cab.
你们现在是认真的吗? 你们想给那个红罗宾家伙下药?
Are you guys serious right now?
You want to drug the Red Robin guy?
我们他妈还有什么别的选择?
What other fucking choice do we have?
“再来一份牛排薯条吗?好!”
"Seconds on steak fries? Uh, yeah!"
拍完第一条后 大家纷纷鼓掌 他们就用了那一条
First take. Everyone applauded. That's the one they used, too.
Fuck it. Let's K-hole the prick.
去他妈的 我们去氯那个混蛋吧
- 就这样 - 加油
-  This is it. -  Yep, let's go. Let's go.
-  All right. -  No way!
- 好的 - 没门
- 没错 中了 来第二个 - 我相信你
That's right, I hit. That's right, I hit.
- Let's go for two. - He's got you believing.
你相信他 来吧 二
Come on, baby. Come on!
投偏了 投偏了 兄弟 你的脚离开了沙发
Bad throw. Bad throw.
Bad throw! Dude, your foot came off the couch.
- 嘿 加里 - 嘿 迪恩 怎么了?
- Oh, hey, Gare. - Oh, hey, Dean, what's up?
嘿 你们看我的红罗宾广告了吗?
Hey, uh, you guys seen my Red Robin commercial yet?
- 看到了 - 是啊 那玩意全国播放
- We did. Yeah, we did. - Yeah. Shit went national.
是啊 真不错
Yeah, I love that.
我在考虑养一只可爱的卡莫多巨蜥
Thinking of getting me a sweet kimono dragon.
不是科莫多吗?
Isn't it 'komodo'?
不 我要养的那个不是 好吗?
No, not the one I'm getting, right?
好吧
- Oh, yeah! -  Off market. All cash.
非法购入 全款现金支付 你们这些垃圾在做什么?
- What are you losers doing? - We're playing a game
我们在玩游戏 规则是 如果你连续接到三颗花生
where if you catch three peanuts in a row,
you get 20 bucks from each of us.
我们每个人就给你二十块钱 你想加入吗?
Why, you want in?
当然要加入了
- Fuck yeah! - Oh?
- 要 - 好的
- Yeah, yeah, yeah! - Okay.
Man, I'll kick all your asses.
兄弟 我会击败你们的
Step right up and get behind the hat.
那就来吧 站到帽子后面 不许作弊
-  No cheating. -  I got this.
我可以的
- Here we go. - You focused?
- 开始了 - 集中注意力
-  Whoa! - Whoa! Boom!
赞!
Wow!
放松 加里 这靠了一点运气 低调点
Relax, Gare. Little bit of luck there.
- Okay. -  Get low.
- Ohh! Yeah. - Ohh! Yes!
- 好! - 漂亮
我跟韦斯一样擅长口活
I'm just as good as Wes at catching nuts in my mouth.
是啊 因为我是同性恋 玩这个游戏真开心
Oh. Right. 'Cause I'm gay.
Yeah.
I'm so happy we're doing this.
好的 这颗会决定胜负
Okay, this one's for all the marbles.
好的 加里 我们开始吧 准备好了吗?
All right, Gary, let's go, buddy. You ready?
准备?一、二...
Ready? One, two...
Three...
三
吧嗒砰!空心球!
Ba-doomp-pow! All net!
我觉得我吃的这个坚果坏了 好苦
I think I ate a bad one.
Bitter.
My sweet boy.
我可爱的孩子 愿神使你像法莲和河玛拿西一样
May God make you like Ephraim and Manasseh.
愿神祝福你并看顾你
May God bless you and watch over you.
Shouldn't we be stopping this?
我们不应该阻止仪式吗?
别担心 那个药还要半小时才会起效
Don't worry, we got about a half hour before it kicks in.
嘿 我知道我是怎么认识他的了
Hey, I figured out how I know him.
He's in those Red Robin commercials.
他出演了红罗宾的广告 “再来一份牛排薯条吗?好!”
"Seconds on steak fries? Uh, yeah!"
兄弟 演得真好 你应该做演员
Dude, that was great. You should be an actor.
所以你们之前从没见过?
So you guys have never met before?
- 没 但... - 是啊 他是我的铁粉
- No, but... - Yeah, just a big fan.
什么鬼?
- 好吧 到时间了 - 好的
- All right, it's time. - Okay.
Oh...
we're going to need a steak knife.
我们需要一把牛排刀
Ha!
Wow! Is this his bris or his bar mitzvah?
这是他的割礼还是成人礼?
好的 万妮克...惠特克
Okay, little vinegar... Whitaker...
他说了“万妮克”吗?
净化我们...诫命...
...has skanctified us with the...
...commandiments... com... condiments...
调味品...
诫命 利用戒律...用诫命...用戒律
...comma... commandments...
With the commander-ments.
With the commandments. Oy...
-  -  He's seems confused.
What the hell? Is he drunk?
什么鬼?他喝醉了?
我不知道 我看见他之前吃花生了
I don't know. I saw him eat a peanut earlier.
Maybe he's having a reaction?
- 也许他过敏了? - 你说半小时
- Man, you said half an hour. - I don't know.
我觉得我可能有耐药性了
I think I might have developed a tolerance.
好的
Okay.
他给我们下达“环视”的命令...
And he hasht given us
the command to...
circumvision!
Hi, fishy-fishy! Oh, to fishy-fishy!
你好 小鱼鱼
小鱼鱼
妈咪 我明天不想去上学
Mommy, I don't want to go to school tomorrow.
天啊!
Oh, my God!
天啊!他对花生过敏!
Oh, my God! He's allergic to peanuts.
她说了什么?
What did she say?
她说他对鸡巴过敏
She said he's allergic to penis.
他肯定入错行了
Oh, he's certainly in the wrong business.
吧嗒砰!
Ba-doomp-pow!
Oh, my God.
天啊 只给他割了一半的包皮
He's only half circumcised.
- 带孩子去医院 - 对 肯定得去医院
Take the kid to the hospital.
- Yes, definitely a hospital. - I could call an ambulance.
我可以叫救护车
不 现在就得完成
No, this has to be done now.
让瑞奇来完成割礼吧
Let Ricky finish it.
瑞奇?什么?不 你疯了吗?
Ricky? What? No! No. Are you insane?
他曾在非洲替博诺基金会工作 给成人切除过包皮
He used to work for Bono's foundation in Africa,
circumcising adults.
Aw.
是的 没错 但那是很久之前的事了
Yeah, he did. But that was so long ago.
而且 给漂亮的非洲鸡巴割包皮
Plus, it's got to be way easier to circumcise
可比给婴儿割简单多了
a gorgeous African penis than a baby penis.
你觉得呢
You would think.
我可以
I can do it.
Uh, Ricky... Ricky! This is a baby we're talking about.
瑞奇 这是要给婴儿割包皮
A real baby. Are you sure?
- 一个真正的婴儿 你确定? - 你在做什么?
Yeah. Yeah. It's not like I'm cutting a diamond.
嗯 又不是切钻石
I'm sure I can pull it off. Pun intended.
我确信我能做到 刚刚是说笑的
不 我们需要经过认证的割礼执行人
No. No! We need a certified mohel, right?
- 对 - 我在Yelp上找一个
- Right. - I'll just look one up on Yelp.
什么?不行 不能在Yelp上找
What? No! No Yelping.
不 我们已经有一名割礼执行人了 他已经说了犹太祷告词
No, we already have a mohel. He's already said the tefilah.
We just need to let Ricky finish it off.
我们只需要让瑞奇收尾就行
妈妈 不行 我带他去医生工作的医院吧
Mom, no, I'm going to take him to a hospital,
where doctors work.
这里有没有人关心我的外孙
Does anyone here care that my grandson
is laying there half circumcised?
躺在那里只割了一半的包皮?
And we're done!
割好了
就一点点包皮
Just a little off the ol' Tiparillo.
下一个轮到谁?萨默海耶斯 过来 这样我就能帮你割包皮了
- Huh. -  Who's next?
Summerhayes, get over here so I can snip off that turtleneck.
Stanicky, you are unbelievable.
斯坦尼奇 你真是太棒了
- 这是你的了 - 不
- All right, this is yours. - No.
Oh, my God, Ricky!
天啊 瑞奇
-  -
耶!
Yes!
Ricky Stanicky, you are even better than advertized.
瑞奇斯坦尼奇 你比他们说的还要好
苏西 我很高兴能帮上忙
Ah, Susan, it's just a pleasure to help you out.
By the way, the kid's got a good-looking schmeckel on him.
孩子的小弟弟很好看
非常大 他会用它好好享乐的
Real hog barrel. He's going to have some fun with that thing.
- 就跟他爸一样 - 是啊
- Takes after his papa. -  Yeah.
Ricky, do you really have to leave already?
你必须今天走吗? 你不能再待一晚吗?
Can't you just stay one more night?
我很想待 小卡莉...但我得走了
I would love to, Carlsbad...
...but I got to go.
Aw...
他要去内罗毕帮忙应对埃博拉
He's going to Nairobi to help out with the Ebola situation.
- Yeah. - Oh.
是啊
Nairobi?
- 内罗毕? - 对
Yeah. I goes where I's needed.
哪里需要 我就去哪里
- 瑞奇 - 那些家伙
Ricky! Ricky!
Those guys.
嗯...
Well...
天啊
Oh, man.
- 好的 再见 瑞奇 - 独一无二
- Okay, bye, Ricky. -  One of a kind.
- 我们屋里见 - 好的 回见
- I'll see you inside. - I'll see you in a minute.
- 屋里见 - 我会帮忙带孩子
I'm going to help with the baby.
Okay.
That was amazing. Incredible.
- 那太精彩了 太棒了 - 你就是个传奇
You are a legend.
那可是世界一流的表演 罗德
That was world class, Rod.
是瑞奇
It's Ricky.
对
- Yeah... - Right.
好的 这是你的佣金
Well, here's your dough.
我们加了些钱 因为你演得太棒了
Uh, we put some extra in there
just 'cause you knocked it out of the park, man.
- 是的 真的 - 是啊 你从哪儿学的割包皮?
- Yes you did. - Yeah.
Where did you learn to circumcise?
Oh, had a job peeling shrimp at Beefsteak Charlie's.
我曾在查理牛排馆做剥虾皮的工作
Okay.
好吧
有人一直在找你 对吧?
- Oh, you blowing up, huh? -
Are you going to get that, or...?
你要接电话 还是...
No. That's just a crazy fan.
不接 只是疯狂粉丝而已
- 现在你有三个疯狂粉丝了 - 没错
Well, now you got three crazy fans.
That's right.
You guys take care.
你们保重
- 好 我们会没事的 - 你也是 保重
- You too! - Yeah, you too.
- We'll be fine. You take care. - Yeah, please.
是啊 一定保重
If you're ever in Atlantic City...
要是你们再来大西洋城...
- Possibly. - We'll let you know.
- 可能会去 - 我们会跟你说的
We'll definitely let you know.
我们绝对会跟你说的
He's good to go.
他可以走了
-  Thanks, Rod. - Thank you.
- 谢谢你 罗德 - 是瑞奇
It's Ricky.
-  Whew! - Yeah!
- 对 - 我饿了 兄弟
- I'm hungry, man. -  Let's feed you.
我们去吃饭吧
I can't believe it worked!
不敢相信这办法成功了 不敢相信这真的成功了!
I can't believe it actually fucking worked.
As much of a nut job as Rod is...
- 罗德虽然疯疯癫癫的... -“是瑞奇”
- Uh, it's Ricky. - Oh, sorry, Ricky.
抱歉 瑞奇
但他成功了 他成功演绎了瑞奇这个人
But he came through. He actually came through.
So that's it, though, right?
就是这样 对吧? 不会再有瑞奇斯坦尼奇了吧?
- Yep. - No more Ricky Stanicky.
不会 我们再也不提他的名字了
No, we are never mentioning his name ever again.
以前用他的名字的时候很有趣吧?
It was fun while it lasted. Right? Okay.
但是时候彻彻底底地 告别这块烫手山芋了
But it's time to get off that rollercoaster once and for all.
是啊 过山车已到站 请从左侧离开
Yep. Ride's over, folks! Please exit to your left!
检查你的物品
Please check for your belongings!
You gotta be this tall to ride this ride.
你得长得足够高才能玩
韦斯 你总是画蛇添足
Wes, you always do one too many, man.
去你的 那是画蛇添足?
Fuck you. Is that one too many?
- Oh, it is. That is too many. - Guys, guys, guys. Guys.
- 那就是画蛇添足 - 各位
各位 最后一次 干杯
For the very last time, a toast...
To Ricky Stanicky.
敬瑞奇斯坦尼奇
To Ricky Stanicky!
我们从未有过的最好的朋友
Best friend we never had.
- You got some on your arm. - Hoo!
你的手臂粘上了一点
不 我是说 这是我刚出生的儿子 这是联络感情
I mean, it's my newborn son, you know,
it's like this bonding thing.
如果其他人朝我撒尿 我会恶心死
If anybody else had pissed on me,
I'd be totally grossed out.
要是苏珊朝你撒尿呢?
What about if it was Susan?
Eew!
各位 去拿杯咖啡 然后进来
Hey, guys, grab a cup of coffee and get in here.
Yes!
好的
昨天的活动太精彩了
Yesterday was a real kick.
It was nice spending time with you guys
跟你们在办公室外共度时光非常愉快
outside the boiler room.
- Mm-hm. - It is.
- 是啊 - 谁不喜欢好的割礼仪式呢?
Who doesn't love a good bris, right?
是吧?我们应该经常搞点活动
Right! We should do it all the time.
- Have a bris? - Hang out. We should hang...
举办割礼?
出去玩 我们应该去...
By the way, your wife, Miriam, she's amazing.
顺便说一句 你的妻子 米里亚姆 她太赞了
- Just fantastic. - A lovely, lovely woman.
- 太棒了 - 一个很可爱的女人
谢谢 她也很喜欢你们
Thanks. She liked you guys too.
你们的朋友斯坦尼奇 真的让她印象深刻
And she was really taken with your friend Stanicky.
那家伙自信而勇敢
He's got brass balls on him, that guy.
她很喜欢他当面怼人的那股劲
She loved how in my face he was.
- 真的吗? - 他就喜欢直来直去 那家伙
Really?
Yeah, he'll give it to you, man, that guy.
是的 那就是瑞奇 是个人物
- That's Ricky. - Yeah. He'll...
- Just... he's a character. - He is a character.
他是个人物 非常强大 伙计
- A powerful creature, man. - He sure is.
当然是了 因此我雇佣了他
That's why I hired him.
太棒了 你他妈刚刚说什么?
- Mm-hm. - Awesome.
What the fuck did you just say?
你他妈刚刚说什么?
I just said, "Awesome."
我刚刚说太棒了
That's awesome.
太棒了
你刚才说...你说什么了?再说一遍
You just said...
What did you say? Just say it one more time?
瑞奇给了我他的电话号码
Ricky gave me his number and when I got home, I called him.
我回家后 给他打了电话
在他上飞机前 我刚好打通了他的电话
I got him right before he got on the plane too.
He came over to my place.
他来到我家
我们一直聊到了凌晨4点 达成了协议
We were up till 4 a.m. banging out a deal.
那个大块头?
The buff guy?
那个穿着狩猎装来参加我儿子的割礼
The guy who wore the safari outfit to my son's bris
并用雪茄刀割了他的包皮的那个人?
and circumcised him with a cigar cutter?
- You banged out a deal? - Yes.
是的 我雇佣了瑞奇斯坦尼奇
I hired Ricky Stanicky.
Wow! Wow!
But do you think... like, he has the experience
但你觉得他有经验吗?
- to be working here? - Yeah, does he, ya think?
是啊 你觉得他有吗?
没有 尽管他缺乏经验
Nah, whatever he lacks in experience,
他积极的能量足以弥补经验的缺失
he more than makes up for with piss and vinegar.
我喜欢他对世界河流交易的看法
I loved his take on the World River deal.
- But that's... - Not his take, really.
- 但那... - 那不是他的想法
Yeah, that's just what he read in the news.
是啊 那只是他在新闻里看到的
Uh-huh.
你们别耍把戏了 两位
You can stop playing games, guys.
我知道是你们雇了他
I know you've been recruiting him.
You don't think I noticed
你们以为我不知道在过去的几个月里
that JT expensed three rounds of golf at Carnegie Abbey
JT报销了卡内基庄园俱乐部的 三轮高尔夫球的费用吗?
in the last couple of months?
我觉得是两轮
That was two rounds, I think...
因为我们在...
B-because we were... we were...
- 我们在招募他... - 招募他
- We were recruiting him. - Recruiting him.
- 我们觉得 他不是萨默海耶斯的料 - 不好
And we decided...
- Not... not good. - Not Summerhayes material.
- 对 他不... - 我觉得他不适合这地方
Yeah, he just doesn't...
I don't think he's right for this place.
Hey! Speak of the devil.
嘿 说曹操 曹操到
Okay.
- 菲利普 - 嗯
- Oh, Philip. - Yeah?
我想要桃花心木或桦木的桌子
I was hoping to see something in a mahogany or a birch.
我觉得这是卡罗莱纳松的 这种木材很垃圾
I believe this is Carolina pine. That's a shit wood.
好的 垃圾木材
Okay. Uh... shit wood...
Philip, can we have a sec?
- 菲利普 能让我们单独聊聊吗? - 好的 请吧
Yes. Please.
Oh, and for these walls,
这些墙壁 我希望把它们漆成 更像火腿的颜色
I'd love to see something in more of a ham color.
Right.
好的
你到底在这里干什么?
What the fuck do you think you're doing here?
太难以置信了 这太棒了 对吧?
This is unbelievable. How cool is this, right?
And I didn't even have to fill out an application!
- 我都不必填写申请表 - 申请表?这不是小凯撒披萨店
Application?! This isn't Little Caesar's.
你绝对不可能 在这里演戏不穿帮的 好吗?
There's no way for you to act your way through this, okay?
这里可没剧本给你
There's no script for you to follow here.
Okay, you guys can help me out.
你们可以帮我
割礼的时候 我帮了你们 这就是朋友的意义
Just like I helped you out in the bris thing, right?
- That's what friends are for. - Friends? We're not friends!
朋友?我们不是朋友
我们的协议是你来演戏 然后离开 你拿到了报酬
The deal was you come to the gig, then you leave.
You got paid.
- 现在滚! - 滚!
- Now go! - Go!
Come on. What was I supposed to do?
我应该怎么办?
萨默斯瓜给我打电话 说:“嘿 伙计”
Your boss, Summersquash, hits me up
- and he's like, "Hey, man." - 'Summerhayes'?
- 萨默海耶斯? - 对 就是他
Yes, that guy.
Offers me 250 large right out of the blue.
他居然给我开出了 二十五万美元的薪资
- 什么? - 二十五万美元?
- What?! - $250,000?
Yeah, but that's for the whole year.
对 不过是年薪
That's more than we make.
- 那比我们的工资还多 - 天啊
Oh, my God!
我曾在索马里做人质谈判员
Well, I did work as a hostage negotiator in Somalia.
So maybe I bring a certain amount of life experience
所以也许我将一些 生活经验带入到了工作中
to the table.
拜托 各位 你们没读过圣经吗?
I mean, come on, guys, didn't you read the bible?
- 圣经就他妈是我们写的! - 是我们写的
- We wrote the fucking bible! - We did that.
罗德 我需要你非常仔细地听我说
Rod, I need you to listen to me very, very carefully.
It's 'Ricky'.
是瑞奇
罗德 听我说 好吗?
Rod! Listen to me, okay?
这事绝对不会有好结果的 好吗?
There's no way that this ends well. All right?
你甚至都不知道我们是做什么的
You don't even know what we do here.
商务事务
It's like business stuff.
你们就像赌注经纪人 对吧?
You guys are like... like bookies, right?
We're not bookies.
我们不是赌注经纪人
不过 要说实质的话 两者是有...
Well, when you boil it down a little bit, there is...
这工作复杂多了 好吗?
It's way more complex than that, okay?
Dean, Erin's in your office. She says it's urgent.
迪恩 艾琳在你的办公室 她说有急事
Hey.
- 嘿 - 他们雇我了
They hired me!
- Who? - MFMBC!
- 谁? - MFMBC
他们想让我去制作《本周英雄》栏目
They want me to produce the 'Hero of the Week' segment.
- MFMBC? - Yes!
- MFMBC? - 对!
你在开玩笑吗?什么?天啊
Are you kidding me? What?!
- Oh, my gosh! Oh. -
- Oh, I'm so proud of you. - Thank you.
- 我为你骄傲 - 谢谢
我不是跟你说过你会有机会吗?
Didn't I tell you you were going to get your big break?
- You did, you did. - You got your big break.
- 是的 - 这不机会就来了
我跟他们说了瑞奇斯坦尼奇的故事 他们很喜欢
You did. I pushed them the Ricky Stanicky story
and they loved it.
- 瑞奇...什么? -《本周英雄》栏目
The Ricky what?
The 'Hero of the Week' segment.
我给他们发了一份提案 讲述了瑞奇在非洲和南美洲的工作
I sent them a proposal about the work Ricky does
in Africa, in South America and how he works with Bono...
以及他如何跟博诺合作 如何帮忙清理那次石油泄漏
...and helped clean up the oil spill
in the Chesapeake Bay, and they want me to produce it!
他们想让我来制作
- Oh! -"Oh"?
- 哦 - 哦?
What's wrong with your face?
你的脸怎么了?
This is my happy face. I'm so... I'm happy.
这是我高兴的脸 我太...高兴了 我...高兴啊
I'm ha... I'm happy.
Great. Because we got to get him back here now.
太好了 因为我们得请他回来
他们想让我这周就报道
They want me to run it this week.
好吧
Right.
我不知道有没有可能请他回来
I don't know if that's going to be... possible.
I don't... There's just a lot of, uh...
- 只是有很多... - 更像是罐装火腿
-  More of a canned ham. - A lot of moving...
- 移动... - 非常接近Spam火腿
- Very close to spam. -  Ricky?
瑞奇?
Ricky!
Man of the Year? Wow! That's so cool!
《年度人物》?这太酷了
不是《年度人物》 是《本周英雄》 而且这并不好
It's not man of the year. It's hero of the week.
And it's not wow. It's a fucking shit show.
现在简直他妈的乱套了!
而且姑娘们今晚 要跟他一起去打保龄球
And on top of that,
the girls are going bowling with him tonight.
- Do we have to go? - Of course we have to go.
- 我们也得去吗? - 当然得去
我们是那个卑鄙小人 最好的朋友 记得吗?
We're the dipshit's best friends, remember?
而且我们不能 让那家伙离开我们的视线
Plus we can't let that fucker out of our sight.
谁知道他会说什么
There's no telling what he'll say.
You know, on the bright side, it is pretty remarkable that,
往好的方面想
我们创造的人物
you know, we invented a man who can win an award like this.
可以获得这种奖项 这很了不起
你觉得他会感谢我们吗?
Hey, you think he'll thank us?
你现在是认真的吗?
Are you fucking serious right now?
韦斯 你抽太多大麻了
Wes! You are smoking way too much weed
你不理解这有多严重 好吗?
if you don't understand how serious this is, okay?
这不再只是我们的事了
It's not just about us anymore.
这可能会毁掉艾琳的职业生涯 醒醒
This could destroy Erin's career. Wake up!
I don't have a choice.
我别无选择
- I got to tell her the truth. - No fucking way!
- 我要告诉她真相 - 不行 迪恩 不可以
- I got to. - Dean, no. Dude!
如果你告诉艾琳 她会告诉苏珊 然后你觉得会发生什么?
If you tell Erin, she'll tell Susan. Okay?
Then what do you think is going to happen?
我错过了我儿子的出生
Not only did I miss the birth of my son,
让一个色情艺人兼彼得弗兰普模仿者
but I let some porno Peter Frampton impersonator
用雪茄刀割了他的包皮 不行
snip his dick with a cigar cutter.
No!
嘿 各位
Hey, guys.
Hey, Karnowski.
- 嘿 卡诺夫斯基 - 雷比莱的演出怎么样?
How was the Rebillet show?
很棒 混蛋 谢谢你的票 谢谢
It was great, you piece of shit. Thanks for the tickets.
Thank you!
Shitbag!
混蛋
不应该这么对他 卡诺夫斯基
He doesn't deserve that. Karnowsk!
Karnowski!
卡诺夫斯基!
-  -
你绝对不可能第二球就补全的
You'll never pick it up.
I like your form.
我喜欢这种形式
看看这家伙 没有任何牵挂
I mean, look at this guy. Not a care in the world.
要是他再提一次他的薪水 我就打爆他的头
If he mentions his salary one more time,
I'm going to hit him in the fucking head.
Well, maybe if you gave him more money
也许如果你给他更多钱 他就会离开
than he's being paid, he'd leave.
韦斯 他的薪水是二十五万美元
He's getting paid $250,000, Wes.
Yeah, but that's for the whole year.
- 但那是年薪 - 我去银行取钱
I'll just run to my bank, then.
我们得想个办法摆脱他 否则我们就完了
We got to figure out a way to get rid of him or we're done.
也许你们不必担心
Look, maybe you're worried about nothing, right?
她只有几天时间来挖掘内幕
She only has a couple of days to dig up dirt.
要是她不挖掘出来 那更糟
If she doesn't dig up dirt, that's worse.
最终 有人会发现真相
Eventually someone's going to find out the truth.
And then Erin would just be one of those journalists
然后艾琳会变成编造新闻的记者
that makes up fake stories.
就像马里奥洛佩兹一样
Yeah, like Mario Lopez.
Oh.
Well, look who's hitting it off.
瞧瞧谁在暗送秋波啊
我以为她跟加里波利斯纳在一起了
I thought she was with Gary Polisner.
Apparently not.
显然没有
Hey, look, none of my business,
听着 这不关我的事
but you should think about chopping that off.
但你应该考虑剪头发
什么?剪头发?
What? A haircut?
我不知道 我害怕剪头发
No, I don't know, I mean, I'd be afraid to.
为什么?你这种脸蛋 应该剪短发
Why? With a face like yours, you should have a pixie.
- 真的吗? - 是的 看看这样
- Really? - Yes! Look at this.
看看这样 看...
Okay...
也许不适合 齐肩或者后背中间更适合
Maybe not.
Down to the shoulders, maybe mid back.
嗯 我觉得...
Yeah, I mean, yeah...
老实说 我早就想剪头发了
Honestly, I've kind of been wanting to cut it for a while,
但我觉得这像是我的特色
but I just feel like this is like my thing now,
and everyone says that they love it.
- 大家都说他们喜欢这长发 - 他们只是表示友好
They're just being nice.
What, really?
什么?真的吗?
是的 信我
Oh, yeah. Trust me.
但他们为什么要对我撒谎?
But why would they lie to me?
I don't know. People are weird, right?
我不知道 人很奇怪 对吧?
Maybe it's hard for them to tell you
他们很难开口告诉你 你看起来傻乎乎的
you look like a freaking loon.
Hey, Carly, whoa.
嘿 小卡
我喜欢你的头发 好吗?
Look, I love your hair. All right?
我想说的是 你要是想剪 就该剪掉
What I was trying to say was,
if you want to cut it, you should.
You shouldn't care about what anybody else thinks.
你不应该在乎其他人的看法
看看你 你很聪明 很可爱
Look at you.
You're smart, you're sweet.
You got that cute little muskrat face.
你有张可爱的麝鼠脸
但所有人都只看到了 你美得令人发狂的头发
But all anybody can ever see is your insane...
...ly beautiful hair.
而这并不是你最大的优点
Which is like the tenth best thing you got going for you.
-  - Agh! Ricky! Ricky!
瑞奇!
Oh, what's happening? Ricky, Ricky, what's happening?
关掉这该死的机器 怎么回事?
What's happen...? Ow!
嘿!别他妈打保龄球了!
Hey! Stop fucking bowling!
救命!
What just happened?
刚刚怎么回事?
卡莉 那太可怕了
Oh, Carly, that was terrible.
Moron! He almost took her head off.
白痴 他差点把她的头砍下来了
就是 他完了
That's it. He's done.
我很乐意支付二十五万 三十万美元 无论多少钱
I'll gladly pay 250, 300, whatever it costs.
I'll get a loan, sell a kidney. Whatever it takes.
我会贷款、卖肾 不惜一切代价 他得离开这里
He's out of here!
等等
Wait a minute.
要是他没能保住 那份年薪二十五万的工作呢?
What if he didn't have a job that paid him 250 grand a year?
Like, if he got fired.
要是他被解雇了呢?
我们面对现实吧 我们需要跟世界河流公司合并
Let's face facts.
We need this merger with World River,
他们似乎 并不在乎这桩交易 为什么?
and they seem to be able to take it or leave it.
Why? Well, I'll tell you why.
我告诉你们原因 那些人来自旧金山
Those folks are from San Francisco
我们是一家老牌新英格兰公司
and we're an old-money New England company.
他们觉得我们是老古董
They think we're dinosaurs.
他们寻求新事物 寻求进取
They're looking for new,
they're looking for progressive.
所以 来吧 我们听听大家的想法
So, come on.  Let's hear some ideas.
Dean, you're point on this. Why don't you get us started?
迪恩 你对此事的看法 你来抛砖引玉吧
事实上 我觉得今天 应该重点听听瑞奇的想法
Actually, I was thinking that Ricky
should take point on this today.
他是我们最新的员工 也是环保英雄
He's our newest employee and he's an 'eco-hero'.
好主意 瑞奇 你有什么想法?
I like that idea. Ricky, what do you got?
Well, thank you for the vote of confidence, Dean.
谢谢你们的认可 当然应该由你来主持会议
You should run the meeting, for sure.
I am just not quite up to speed.
我只是还没跟上进度
- 有道理 - 他有一些大计划
Well, that makes sense.
But Ricky's got something big worked out here.
你怎么说的来着? 游戏规则改变者 对吧?
What'd you call it? Um... game changer, right?
游戏规则改变者?肯定很不错 瑞奇 你有什么想法?
Game changer. Got to love that. Ricky, what do you got?
我...
I, um...
I, er...
瑞奇 我23分钟后要吃午饭
Rick, I have a lunch in 23 minutes.
Yeah.
嗯
好的
Okay.
Um...
My area of expertize is in non-profit humanitarian work.
我的专业领域 是非营利人道主义工作
简而言之 我是一个心怀世界的人
In short, I'm a world hugger.
所以 为何我们 不把我那令人兴奋的背景
So, you know, why don't we bring my exciting background
带到无聊的投资产品世界呢?
to the boring-ass world of investment products?
女士们先生们 以盈利为目的就一定是为了盈利吗?
I mean, you know, ladies and gentlemen,
does for-profit have to be for profit?
总体思路就是这样
Well, that's the general idea.
正确 那位身穿 保守灰色西装的绅士得十分
Correct!
Ten points to the gentleman in the conservative grey suit.
Er, could you please elaborate?
你能详细说说吗?
我刚才说的意思是...
What I was saying...
如果我们把我们赚的所有钱 都捐给穷人之类的呢?
...was, what if we took all the money we made
and gave it away to poor people and shit?
I'm not sure I understand that.
我不确定我是否理解了这一点
- And shit. - I know I don't.
我知道我不理解
Well, think about it.
想想看
如果我们像保罗纽曼生产沙拉酱那样
If we became, um, like the Paul-Newman-salad-dressing
of banks,
the whole world would like us.
全世界都会喜欢我们
That is the stupidest idea I've ever heard.
这是我听过的最蠢的想法
Well, now, wait a minute.
现在 等等 想想这话蕴含的意义 比林斯
Read between the lines, Billings.
这正是我要说的事
This is exactly what I've been talking about.
斯坦尼奇说的是我们必须改变现状
Stanicky's saying we got to shake things up.
尝试不同的东西
Try something different.
No, that's not what he's saying. He's saying...
不 他不是这意思...
汤姆斯公司的例子呢?
What about that Tom's company?
每售出一双鞋 就免费送一双
Giving away a free pair of shoes for every pair sold.
我打赌这最初 听起来是一个愚蠢的想法
I bet that sounded like a stupid idea at first.
And what are they clearing?
但执行以后结果如何?
去年收入1.7亿美元
170 million in revenue last year.
1.7亿美元 非常惊人
170 million. That's impressive.
显然 我们不能捐出所有钱
Now, obviously, we can't give away all our money,
but we could funnel some of it into philanthropic ventures.
但我们可以将其中一部分 投入到慈善事业中
而且这样肯定会有税收优惠
And there have got to be tax incentives.
对 税收那破玩意
- Yeah! Tax shit. - Yeah.
我们可以称其为“好感投资”
We could call it, um... Feel-Good Investing.
我们向公众展示 我们是一家有社会责任感的公司
We'll show people we're a company that cares.
Feel-Good Investing. I like that. Great work, Rick.
“好感投资” 我喜欢 干得好 瑞奇!
Thanks, Ted.
谢谢你 特德
What did you say, Ricky?
你刚说什么 瑞奇?
Oh... nothing.
没什么 我只是对那个人说“去你的”
I was just saying "fuck you" to that guy.
对 去你的 比林斯
Yeah, fuck you, Billings!
We're just kidding.
我们开玩笑的 但去你的 比林斯
But fuck you, Billings.
我们接下来的安排
Here's what we're going to do.
让世界河流公司的人周三下午飞过来
The World River folks are flying in Wednesday afternoon.
Wednesday? What? Why Wednesday?
周三?为什么是周三?
因为周三晚上 我们将在我的俱乐部举行峰会
Because Wednesday night
we're going to have a little summit over at my club
一起观看瑞奇的《本周英雄》环节
and watch Ricky's 'Hero of the Week' segment.
俱乐部 好耶!
Clubs ahoy!
Right.
好的 我想让你们带上家人 和你们最好的状态过来
Now, I want you to bring your families and your A-games.
周三 我们会给这些人看看我们是谁
Wednesday, we're going to show these people who we are.
我们很现代 很有趣
We're modern, we're fun, we're socially conscious,
我们有社会意识 而且是美国英雄
and we're American heroes.
- What is happening right now? - I don't know.
现在是什么情况?
我觉得像是《黑钱胜地》里 每一集的杰森贝特曼
I feel like Jason Bateman in every episode of 'Ozark'.
Hey, boss-man? Er, got a minute?
嘿 老大 有空吗?
Sure!
有啊
Dean! JT! What it do?
迪恩 JT 你们好吗?
What the...? What are you doing here?
你在这里做什么?
Ricky hired me.
瑞奇雇佣了我
雇你做什么?
- To do what? - I don't know.
我不知道 我猜是雇我来帮他之类的
Help him out with stuff, I guess.
对 我觉得年轻的韦斯利 作为我的随员表现出了巨大的潜力
Yes, I think young Wesley shows great promise
as my attaché.
谁是你的随员 迪恩?
- Who's your attaché, Dean? - I don't have an attaché.
我没有随员 我不是外交官
I'm not a foreign diplomat.
Listen, you and me need to have a chat.
听我说 你和我必须谈谈
好的 但我们谈话前 我想给你们看些东西
Okay, but before we do, I want to show you something.
First, thank you for having faith
首先 谢谢你今天对我的信任
and believing in me today.
如果不是你把我扔进火坑里 我永远都想不出那些主意
I never would've come up with those ideas in the meeting
if you hadn't thrown me into the fire.
乐意效劳 兄弟
Happy to do it, man.
我觉得我知道问题出在哪里了
I think I figured out what the problem is.
什么问题?
What problem?
整个合并无法推进下去的问题
The whole 'not getting the merger' thingy problem.
你参加了一场员工会议 然后就搞清楚了?
You went to one staff meeting
and you've got the whole company figured out?
所以我今早用手机拍了这个 我的随员把它上传到电脑上
So I filmed this on my phone in the staff meeting this morning
and my attaché put it on the computer.
So, check it out.
你们看看
- ...San Francisco and we... -  See?
看到了吗?
- ...old-money New England... - You see?
- They're looking for... - See what?
- 看到什么? - 这个人是世界级的空鸡巴侠
The guy's a world-class air-dicker.
空什么?你在说什么?
An air what-er? What are you talking about?
继续看
Keep watching.
他每次试着阐明一个观点时
Every time he tries to make a point,
it's like he puts an invisible penis in his mouth.
他就像把一个 隐形的鸡巴放进嘴里一样
Remember when Obama used to power knuckle
还记得奥巴马使用权力关节 来提出观点吗?
to try to make that point?
萨默海耶斯也做了同样的事
Well, Summerhayes does the same thing,
但他的动作像在吸一个隐形的鸡巴
but when he does it, it's like he's smoking invisible dongs.
天啊 他是个空鸡巴侠
Oh, my God, he is an air-dicker.
这种习惯会在特定时间和地点出现 但很难摆脱
There's a time and a place for it,
but it's really hard to get away with it
in a business setting.
Yo, let's make a TikTok out of this!
我们用它发个短视频吧
What do you guys think? Should I tell him?
你们觉得呢?我应该告诉他吗?
Tell him what?
告诉他什么?
That he's a world-class air-dicker.
说他是世界级的空鸡巴侠
- 当然了 - 你应该说
- Absolutely. - Yeah, you should.
你怎么能替他工作?
How could you work for him, dude?
在他几乎要毁掉我们的人生的时候 你却给他打工
We don't need you exploring career opportunities
when he's trying to ruin our lives.
首先 他没毁掉我的生活 他真的很在乎我
First of all, he's not ruining my life.
He hired me 'cause he actually gives a shit.
如果我不找份工作 基思就会甩了我
If I didn't get off my ass and get a job,
Keith was going to dump me.
我注意到我所谓的真正的朋友 从没给过我工作
By the way, I noticed that my so-called real friends
never offered me a job.
你他妈在开玩笑吗?
Are you fucking shitting me?!
You two!
你们俩!立刻进来!
In here, now!
进来 坐下
Come in, sit down.
给他们看你给我看的东西
Show them what you showed me.
I already did, Ted.
我已经给他们看了 特德
你们知道这件事 却从来只字不提?
You knew about this and you never said anything?
- 我们只是觉得... - 这只是一种习惯而已
Well, we just thought it was...
It's just a mannerism. It's really not that big of a deal.
这没什么大不了的 特别是在今时今日
Especially in this day and age.
我知道这没什么大不了的 我有两个儿子是弯的 天啊
I know it's not a big deal!
Two of my sons are gay, for Christ's sake!
第三个是直是弯正在探索中
And the third one's just... working it out.
但我不能这么参加会议
But I can't go into meetings like this.
难怪他们对合并不感兴趣
No wonder they're not interested in the merger.
他们会被分散注意力 我说的话 一个字都听不进去
They're so flippin' distracted,
they haven't heard a word I've said.
我们不知道你在哪儿都会做这种动作
We don't know that you've been doing this everywhere. I...
据我们所知 你只是在今天的会议上有这动作
As far as we know, you just did it in today's meeting.
我之前从没见过
I'd never seen it before.
真的吗?
- Really? -
我找到那次的会议链接了
I've got the conference link.
This merger will allow us
这次合并将使我们
to further enhance our capital efficiencies.
进一步提高我们的资本效率
- Look at you. - Oh, God...
- 看看你 左右做空鸡巴动作 - 天啊
Air-dicking left and right.
有些公司想要变大变强
There are companies out there who want to get bigger.
有些公司想要缩小规模
There are companies out there who want to get smaller.
在10秒内 你就做了四次
You just air-dicked four times in ten seconds.
亲爱的上帝啊 这是真的
Oh, dear God, it's true.
On the other hand, to support everything we do...
另一方面 为了支持我们做的一切...
天啊!现在这动作 看起来像是我在托着蛋蛋
Oh, God! Now it looks like I'm cupping the balls.
...凭借知识和计划
...with knowledge and planning.
Oh!
嘿 你在撸两根管
Hey, you're double-dongin' it.
...is the company that can do both.
...公司可以做到这两点
天啊 把它拿出去...关掉
Oh, God. Get it... Turn it off.
有些人说...
- Some people say... -
Okay, from this point forward
好的 从现在开始 斯坦尼奇负责合并事宜
Stanicky is in charge of the merger.
什么?
What? Ted, come on.
特德 拜托 我为了合并忙活了九个月
I've been running point on this for nine months.
Yeah, and look where it's gotten us.
是的 看看现在的进展! 他才来这儿一天...
He's been here one day and...
- 小心空鸡巴 特德 - 天啊!
- Watch the air-dicking, Ted. - Jesus...!
Here's the bottom line.
最重要的是
无论是好事还是坏事 斯坦尼奇会直接告诉我
Stanicky gives it to me straight,
whether the news is good or bad.
他来负责 讨论完毕
He's in charge. End of discussion.
Oh, Jesus. Okay, just make it go away. Just...
天啊!
好了 别放了 让它黑屏吧
- Yep. - Go to black.
把它关了
- Oh, er... - Just go to black.
我在按了 它不...
Yeah, I'm pressing it but it's not...
把它给...我不知道怎么操作这玩意
- Give it to me. - Yeah, try...
I don't know how to work this thing.
- No, I know. - Is there an IT guy?
- 有技术人员吗? - 我就是
- That's me. - Argh, fuck!
操!
迪恩
Oh, Dean...
尽管特德在办公室里说让我负责
Despite what Ted said back there,
about me being in charge,
但我不会假装 自己比你更了解这家公司
I don't pretend to know more about this company than you.
我假装自己比你懂得多
Well, I pretend to know more than you,
但你显然比我更清楚公司的情况
but you are clearly
more informed in company matters than me
现在 我需要你的专业知识
and right now I need your expertize.
What?
- 什么? - 我要录下来 免得忘了 好吗?
I don't want to forget this. Okay...
我应该要求加薪多少?
How big of a raise should I be asking for?
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
操 他妈的!
你要辞职!今天就辞!
You're quitting! Today!
- 你在说什么? - 演出结束了 罗德
- What are you talking about? - Show's over, Rod.
It's Ricky.
是瑞奇
It's not Ricky, okay? Get it through your head, man.
不是瑞奇!好吗?
你给我记清楚 伙计! 瑞奇斯坦尼奇不是真的!
Ricky Stanicky isn't real.
Yes, he is. Here.
他是真的 就在这里
Richard Barbara Stanicky?
“理查德芭芭拉斯坦尼奇”?
That's my grandmother's name.
那是我祖母的名字
Where the fuck did you get this?
你到底从哪儿弄到这身份证的?
我正式改名了
Officially changed my name.
Paid to expedite it online. They overnighted it.
在线支付了加急费 隔夜就弄好了
Oh, my God.
天啊
拜托 迪恩 从我的角度想想
Come on, Dean. See this from my side.
我天生就是扮演这个角色的料 我现在演得非常好
This is the role I was born to play and I'm nailing it.
不 你是在欺诈的前提下被雇佣的
No, you were hired under false pretences.
- 你对他们撒谎了 - 没有 迪恩 是你对他们撒谎了
You lied to them.
No, as I recall, Dean, you lied to them.
Oh, ha, ha, ha. You got me there.
你难住我了
But you know what? This is different.
这不一样 你让大家的 职业生涯岌岌可危
You're putting people's careers at risk.
职业生涯?我就来了两天 而我成了你的上司
Careers?
I've been here two days and I'm your boss.
我说的是艾琳的职业生涯!
I'm talking about Erin's career!
你可以用正义的说辞愚弄萨默海耶斯
You can fool Summerhayes with this righteous shit.
但我知道你的真实身份
But I know who you really are.
你是硬摇滚罗德 是个酒鬼!
You're Rock Hard Rod! The drunk.
Yeah.
对
I was a drunk.
我以前是个酒鬼
没人尊重我 我的工作糟透了 没有朋友
Nobody respected me. My job sucked. I had no friends.
但现在我拥有了这一切
But now I have all those things.
And I'm sober. All right?
而且我戒酒了 好吗?
要是我离开这里 这一切都会消失
And if I leave here, it all goes away.
My whole life, all I've ever been is a shit baby.
我的一生 我一直是个大便婴儿
And now I get to be somebody people actually like.
而现在 我成了人们真正喜欢的人
Don't take that away from me, man. Please.
别剥夺我的这个身份 求你了
听着 这件事必须做个了结
Look, this has to end.
-  -
你到底在干什么?住手
What the fuck are you doing? Stop! Stop! Hey, hey!
住手 嘿 什么...停 住手!
-  - Argh! Hey, okay!
要是我回去 他们会杀了我
If I go back, they'll kill me. If I go back, they'll kill me.
什么?
What?!
要是我回大西洋城 他们会杀了我
If I go back to Atlantic City, they'll kill me.
谁?
- Who? - The Sasquatch
赌场的大脚野人和他的朋友乔佩西
and his Joe Pesce buddy from the casino.
I told you they were crazy fans.
我跟你说他们是疯狂粉丝 他们确实很疯 但不是粉丝
They're crazy. They're not fans.
Why? What did you do?
为什么?你做了什么?
我不知道
I don't know.
我以前喝酒经常喝到断片 什么事都有可能
I used to drink and black out, it could be anything.
一天 我从一顿狂饮后醒过来
One day I woke up after a five-day bender,
发现自己成了一家快餐店的经理
I was a manager of an Arby's.
Plus, I owe a lot of bad people a lot of money.
而且 我还欠了很多坏人很多钱
所以...
You were right, man.
你说得对 这是我的错
It's my fault.
这是我的错
It's... it's my fault.
Wow.
我曾经拥有一切
I had everything.
I had good friends. I had a great job.
我曾经拥有好朋友 好工作
世界上最善良
The most kind-hearted,
也是最漂亮的人爱着我
beautiful person in the whole world loved me.
遇见艾琳是我这一生最美好的事
Erin's the best thing that ever happened to me.
我会失去一切
I'm going to lose it all.
♪ She gave you flowers ♪
♪ She gave you Pretty melodies... ♪
我永远都不会理解 你为什么不直接告诉她真相
I'll never understand why you don't just tell her the truth.
我觉得现在说出真相有点晚了 韦斯
I think it's a little late for that, Wes.
不 还不晚
No, it's not.
以上就是史蒂夫史密斯 在华盛顿带来的报道
That was Steve Smith in Washington.
明晚七点 我们将推出《本周英雄》
And tomorrow night at 7 p.m.
we present our Hero of the Week.
Seconds on steak fries? Uh, yeah!
再来一份牛排薯条吗?好
Visit your local Red Robin
前往当地红罗宾 试试我们的无限量牛排薯条
to try our new bottomless steak fries.
I swear to God, man,
斯坦尼奇就像是恶作剧生日蜡烛
Stanicky's like one of those trick birthday candles -
无论我多努力地想把他吹灭 他总会重新燃起来
no matter how hard I try to blow him out,
he just keeps coming back.
Dean, I love you like a brother,
迪恩 我爱你就像亲兄弟一样 但你有一个大缺点
but you got one major flaw.
Hmm?
You lie too much.
你撒太多谎了
I lie too much?
我撒太多谎了?什么... 你撒的谎跟我撒的一样多
What the...?
You lie just as much as me.
Only 'cause you make me.
都是你让我撒的
I've been trying to tell the truth on this one
我从一开始就试着说出真相
from the beginning,
但你拒绝了
but you said no.
因为我不想让JT惹上麻烦
Because I was looking out for JT.
I didn't want JT to get in trouble.
兄弟 这跟JT无关
Dude, this has nothing to do with JT.
这一切都与你有关
This has everything to do with you.
你意识到了吗 罗德将原本虚假的人生变成了真的
Do you realize that Rod had a fake life and he made it real?
你却将原本真实的人生变成了假的
You had a real life and you made it fake.
Fuck this, man. I don't need this shit.
去你的 我不需要你的说教 你没让事情好转
You're not making anything better.
我知道你没掉进沟里
Yo, I know you ain't fall in no ditch.
什么?
What?
我知道你没掉进沟里
I know you didn't fall in a ditch, that one Halloween.
那年万圣节 你摔断手臂的那次
When you broke your arm.
我们朝那栋房子扔了鸡蛋以后
After we egged that house,
我们朝不同方向分头逃跑
and we all split in different directions,
我回去了你家 看你是否在那儿
I went back to your place to see if you was there,
而你在家 我听到了他的声音
and you were.
And I heard him.
I heard what he did to you.
我听到了他对你做了什么
那是一次意外 他喝醉了
That was an accident. He was drunk.
看吧?你又来了 你在撒谎
See, there you go again. You're lying.
兄弟 我知道你小时候过得不幸福
Dude, I understand you grew up in a fucked-up house
知道你有一个变态的父亲
and you had a fucked-up father,
这就是为何你在我和JT家过夜
and that's why you slept over at me and JT's house,
这就是为何你开始撒谎 为了保护自己
and that's probably why you started a lie.
To protect yourself.
But you're not that boy anymore,
但你已不再是那个孩子了
你让那些糟糕的事情 把你变成了一个糟糕的人
and you're letting this shitty stuff
turn you into a shitty person, and that's not you.
你只需要告诉艾琳真相 她不会伤害你的
If you just tell Erin the truth,
she won't hurt you.
♪ Night has fallen quickly On the carnival in town ♪
♪ The cotton candy maker ♪
♪ Is the last To leave the ground ♪
♪ Shuts his tiny wagon ♪
♪ And goes to A room somewhere ♪
♪ His life's Like cotton candy ♪
♪ An illusion Not much there... ♪
Hey. Where were you?
嘿 你去哪儿了?我很担心你
I was worried about you.
I tried to call you.
我给你打了电话
Listen, Erin...
听我说 艾琳...
...you can't let them run your story.
你不能让他们发布你的报道
Yeah, well, it's a little too late for that.
嗯 现在说这话有点太晚了
No, you don't understand.
不 你不明白
你有办法推迟报道或者抢占报道吗?
Is there a way that you can postpone it or pre-empt it?
Is that what they say in your business? 'Pre-empt'?
他们是这么说的吗?“抢占”?
关于瑞奇 有很多事你需要知道
'Cause there's a lot of things
that you need to know about Ricky.
你是说硬摇滚罗德吗?
You mean Rock Hard Rod?
别那么惊讶 迪恩
Don't look so surprised, Dean.
I'm a good reporter, you said so yourself, remember?
我是一个好记者 你自己也说过 记得吗?
- 是的 我知道你是好记者 - 我在割礼仪式上知道的
Yeah, I know you are.
I figured it out at the bris.
Nairobi?
内罗毕?
你说他必须飞回去帮助抗击埃博拉
You said he had to fly back to help fight Ebola,
但过去四年里 没有任何地方爆发过埃博拉病毒
but there hasn't been an Ebola case
anywhere in the last four years
而且内罗毕也绝不会有 他们其实现在已经有疫苗了
and definitely never in Nairobi.
They actually have a vaccine now.
That's good.
那挺好
瑞奇给我看了你们的圣经
Ricky showed me your bible.
太可悲了
It's pathetic.
你们撒谎 只是为了去小联盟世界系列赛
You guys lied so you could
go to the Little League World Series,
勒保斯基节、一个小火车博物馆?
the Lebowski Fest, a tiny train museum.
韦斯喜欢火车
Wes likes trains.
你们去了多莉山主题公园两次
You went to Dollywood, twice!
你为什么不带我一起去? 我很喜欢多莉帕顿
Why didn't you take me with you? I love Dolly Parton.
- 对不起 我不知道 - 比起撒谎 更让我难受的是
I'm sorry. I didn't know that.
What bothers me more than the lies
你第一反应要撒谎的原因
is why you told them in the first place.
You were running from me.
你在逃避我
- 逃避我们 - 没有
From us.
No. No, that's not true.
不 不是的
Well, it doesn't matter anymore, Dean.
好吧 这已经不重要了 迪恩
It's too late.
为时已晚
我只希望这一天结束
I just want this day to be over.
我也是 如果他退缩了呢? 万一他放我们鸽子了呢?
Me too.
What if he chickened out? What if he's going to bail on us?
迪恩在哪里?
Where is Dean?
他在...他一会儿就到
He's, uh, on his... He'll be here any minute.
瑞奇在哪儿?世界河流的高管想见他
And where is Ricky?
The World River execs want to meet him.
他也在路上 他的随员在这儿 所以...
Also on his way. His attaché is here, so...
嗨
Hi.
我们说到哪儿了?
So, where were we?
嘿
Hey!
Where the hell have you been?
你到底去哪儿了?
The show starts in three minutes.
萨默海耶斯想让瑞奇来介绍节目 那家伙在哪里?
Summerhayes wants Ricky to introduce it.
- Where is this guy? - There's no show.
没有节目
What?
什么?
瑞奇永远都不会上《本周英雄》了 艾琳一直都知情
Ricky was never going to be Hero of the Week.
Erin knew all along.
知道什么?
Knew what?
知道瑞奇是假的 她在割礼仪式上就知道了
That Ricky was a fake. She figured it out at the bris.
所以她骗了我们?那可太卑鄙了
So she was lying to us?
Well, that's pretty fuckin' low.
Are you an idiot?
你是不是傻?
我们怎么跟萨默海耶斯说?
What are we going to tell Summerhayes?
The truth.
说实话
Dean, come on. Don't do that. Dean!
迪恩 拜托 别这样 迪恩!
Good evening, everyone.
大家晚上好
感谢各位光临 谢谢
Thank you all for coming out. Thank you.
-  - Thank you.
谢谢 我看到今晚这里有很多老朋友
I see a lot of old friends out here tonight,
还有很多新朋友
and a lot of new friends.
我看到两家很厉害的...
And I see two great companies
that can...
可以成就伟业的公司
...can, uh, do wonderful things.
我希望那个风云人物 瑞奇斯坦尼奇
I was hoping that the man of the hour, Ricky Stanicky,
会在这里介绍 MFMBC的《英雄》栏目
would be here to introduce this MFMBC Heroes segment.
- Ted, can I say something? - Yes, absolutely. Yes, please.
- 特德 我能说几句吗? - 好 当然可以 请吧
这位是迪恩斯坦顿 我们的投资者关系副总 迪恩
Dean Stanton,
our Vice President of Investor Relations.
Dean.
Um...
不幸的是 MFMBC已经决定 不将瑞奇斯坦尼奇列为英雄
Unfortunately, MFMBC has decided
not to profile Ricky Stanicky as a hero.
- Ha... -
The reason being...
因为瑞奇斯坦尼奇并不是英雄
...that Ricky Stanicky's not a hero.
他甚至都不是一个真实的人
He's not even a real person.
- 什么? - 我不理解
I made him up.
他是我塑造的人物
Motherfucker!
混蛋!
I lied to all of you.
我对你们所有人撒谎了
我没有任何借口
And I have no excuses.
对不起 特德
I'm sorry, Ted.
You don't deserve this.
你不应落到这个境地
我也想向每个 从旧金山来到这里的人道歉
I'd also like to apologize to everyone
who came out here from San Francisco.
Summerhayes Financial is an excellent company.
萨默海耶斯金融公司 是一家优秀的公司
请不要因为我的行为 而毁了这段良好的合作伙伴关系
Please don't let my actions destroy
what could be a great partnership.
What the fuck did he just say?
他刚刚到底在说什么?
I don't know what to do.
我不知道该怎么办
我就跟你说吧
I told you...
Where is that pumpkin-headed piece of shit?
那个长着南瓜头的混蛋在哪儿?
I don't get it.
我不理解
If the show wasn't for real,
要是节目的事不是真的 那为什么新闻组的人要过来采访?
then why'd the news crew come in?
- 什么新闻组? - 昨天
- What news crew? - Yesterday.
你吃午饭时 节目组来采访瑞奇了
While you were at lunch,
this crew came in and interviewed Ricky.
我帮忙安排了整个采访事宜
I helped set the whole thing up.
迪恩 不用费心清理你的办公室了
Dean, don't worry about cleaning out your office.
我们会帮你装箱 然后全部烧掉
We'll box it up for ya...
and then burn it.
I'm standing outside the offices
我正站在萨默海耶斯金融公司的 办公楼外
of Summerhayes Financial,
这是一个受人尊敬的机构 位于罗德岛普罗维斯登市中心
an esteemed institution
in downtown Providence, Rhode Island.
那是理查德芭芭拉斯坦尼奇
And that is Richard Barbara Stanicky.
把我们想象成赌注经纪人 而你是赌徒
Think of us as the bookies and you're the gambler.
我们不会打断你的腿 把你从桥上扔下去
We're the nice bookies, not the throw-you-off-the bridge type.
After several years helping the less...
在从事几年援助...
为什么还在放节目?
Why the hell is this still on?!
...charity, he's now the newest
...他现在是
萨默海耶斯金融公司 最新且薪酬最高的高管之一
and one of the most highly paid executives
at Summerhayes Financial.
Where's the AV guy?
- 负责放视频的人在哪里? - 我负责
- Oh, that's me. - I thought you were the IT guy.
- 我以为你是技术人员 - 两个职位都是我
I'm both.
But there's something you should know
但对于这位非常成功的高管 有些事你应该知道
about this highly successful executive.
He's a complete fraud.
他是个彻头彻尾的骗子
I'm Ted Summerhayes...
我是特德萨默海耶斯 而...
That's right.
没错 瑞奇斯坦尼奇 真名叫罗德尼莱姆斯特德
Ricky Stanicky is actually Rodney Rimestead,
是新泽西州大西洋城的 一名色情摇滚模仿者
a pornographic rock'n'roll impersonator
from Atlantic City, New Jersey,
艺名为“硬摇滚罗德”
who goes by the name of Rock Hard Rod.
我们采访了莱姆斯特德先生
We caught up with Mr. Rimestead to find out how he came to be
了解他是如何 成为商人瑞奇斯坦尼奇的
the businessman 'Ricky Stanicky'.
I was hanging around a casino bar in Atlantic City.
我当时在大西洋城的赌场酒吧玩
没钱、没朋友 也没人尊重我 我曾是一个酒鬼
No money, no friends, no respect.
I was an alcoholic.
I am... I am an alcoholic.
现在也是
And I was doing whatever I could to get by.
我竭尽所能维持生计
♪ Cum a, cum a, cum a Come in my sock again ♪
视频由大西洋城老虎机沼泽赌场提供
♪ It's filled with loads ♪
天啊!
Oh, God.
♪ It's filled with loads... ♪
And that night, I met Dean Stanton and his friends.
那晚 我遇见了 迪恩斯坦顿和他的朋友们
他们给我买了吃的和喝的
They bought me food, drink.
他们问我是谁 他们似乎很关心我
They asked me who I was, they really seemed to care.
罗德发现 他们确实很关心他
And as Rod would discover, they did care.
Dean!
迪恩 你得看这个
You got to see this!
Within days, Dean Stanton and his friends
几天后 迪恩斯坦顿和他的朋友们 再次联系了我
would reach out again.
我简直不敢相信他们打来电话了
I couldn't believe they called.
这些我只见过一次 而且只见了几分钟的人
These are people I met only once
and only for a few minutes,
他们给了我一个一生难得的机会
and here they were offering me the opportunity of a lifetime.
是什么机会呢? 那就是扮演瑞奇斯坦尼奇
And what was that opportunity?
Simply to become 'Ricky Stanicky'.
They said, "You are no longer Rod Rimestead,
他们说:“你不再是 罗德莱姆斯特德 失败者
"the loser.
“从现在起 你是瑞奇斯坦尼奇 大赢家”
"From here on out, you're Ricky Stanicky, the winner."
That was the first time
这是第一次有人相信我
somebody had ever believed in me.
罗德 也就是现在的瑞奇 到普罗维登斯安顿好后
After relocating Rod, now Ricky, to Providence,
迪恩斯坦顿和朋友们着手
Dean Stanton and friends set about creating a new identity
为这个曾经担任限制级 狗狗表演主持人的男人创造新身份
for the man who'd once MC'ed an X-rated dog show.
事前警告 下一段视频 可能会让一些观众感到不适
We caution you -
this next video may be disturbing to some viewers.
♪ It's a beautiful night
这是一个美丽的夜晚 所有星星都在闪耀
♪ All the stars Shining bright... ♪
为我的狗狗一起呻吟
Oh, my God!
月亮升起 熠熠生辉...
他们给了我一本书 他们称之为圣经
They gave me a book. They called it their bible.
那就像是瑞奇斯坦尼奇 这个身份的生活蓝图
It was like a blueprint for how to live as Ricky Stanicky.
如何过上美好生活 如何从错误中学习
How to live a good life.
How to learn from your errors.
我看到了自己可以成为什么人 自己错过了什么
I saw what I could have been.
What I'd missed.
And the more and more I read their bible,
随着我深入阅读他们的圣经
the more I realized
我发现这不必只是一个梦
this doesn't have to be just a dream.
所以瑞奇戒酒了 并开始尊重自己
And so 'Ricky' stopped drinking
and started respecting himself.
很快 他在萨默海耶斯金融公司 找到了一份工作
Soon he had a job here at Summerhayes Financial.
迪恩把我介绍给特德萨默海耶斯
Dean introduced me to Ted Summerhayes.
他是那种会拿出超级游艇 来向你展示其富有程度的
He's one of those rich guys
who's gotta whip out his big swinging super-yacht
富豪之一
- to show you how rich he is. - Oh, God...
但另一方面 这家伙 有一颗金子般的心
But, on the other hand, the guy's got a heart of gold.
我们启动了“好感投资”计划
We started Feel-Good Investing.
And then, through Dean, I met more and more friends.
然后通过迪恩 我认识了越来越多的朋友
我认识了一个人美心善的姑娘
I met a beautiful girl, with a beautiful soul.
Aw.
我有了自己的生活 成为了瑞奇斯坦尼奇
And I had a life.
I became 'Ricky Stanicky'.
然而 在这一切之中
And somewhere in the middle of it all,
神话和现实之间的界线已经模糊
the line between the mythical and the real had blurred.
就这样 很不可思议 一个大西洋城的醉鬼弃儿
And that's how, improbably, a drunken Atlantic City reject
发现自己有幸在海洋州开始新的生活
found himself blessed with a new life in the Ocean State.
Hero? Me? No. No.
英雄?我吗?我不是
如果这个故事中要找一个英雄 那就是救了我的男人们
If there's a hero to this story,
it's the men who saved my life.
迪恩斯坦顿 JT莱文和韦斯什么来着
Dean Stanton, JT Levine and Wes... something.
A story that started out fraudulently,
这是一段以欺诈开始的故事
然而它奇迹般地
somehow, miraculously,
变成了一段救赎、重生与爱的故事
became a tale of redemption, rebirth and love.
Because he believed that anybody at any time
因为他相信任何时候 任何人
都能成为他们想成为的人
can become the person they want to be,
我们选择瑞奇斯坦尼奇 作为我们的本周英雄
we choose Ricky Stanicky as our Hero of the Week.
去吧 瑞奇!
Ricky! Ricky! Ricky!
瑞奇!
♪ If you're going to San Francisco... ♪
你是在逆境中成功翻盘了
Well...
you came out of this smelling like a rose, didn't ya?
How do you think it makes me look?
你觉得那让我看起来成什么人了?
你在开玩笑吗?
Are you kidding me?!
特德 这是一个 多么美妙而励志的故事啊
Such a wonderful and inspirational story, Ted.
Great job Ted, and you too, Dean.
干得好 特德 你也是 迪恩
Oh, I... I didn't do it.
我没做...
萨默海耶斯 我喜欢你雇佣的这些人
Summerhayes. I like the people you surround yourself with.
I mean, the concept of second chances
第二次机会的概念 以及你推出的好感投资
and feeling good about your investments -
这正是我们在努力实现的目标
that's something we're trying to achieve.
那就是我们在做的事
Well, that's... what we do.
事实是 是特德看到了瑞奇的潜力
Truth is, it was Ted who saw the potential in Ricky.
而且与更多慈善组织合作 也是他的主意
It was also his idea to start partnering
with more charitable organizations.
- I just saw the tax incentives. -
我只是看到了税收优惠
You're a humble son of a bitch, aren't ya?
你真是个谦虚的小王八蛋 对吧?
Ah...
那我们达成协议了?
So, do we have a deal?
我不知道 迪恩 你觉得呢?
I don't know.
Dean, what do you think?
We have a deal.
- 我们成交 - 当然 我们要合作 谢谢
- Absolutely, we have a deal. - Yeah, we have a deal.
- 太好了 - 谢谢
- Great. - Wonderful.
你让你虚构的朋友 给我们的孩子割包皮?
You let your made-up friend circumcise our child?
亲爱的 他曾在查理牛排店工作
Honey, he worked at Beefsteak Charlie's.
牛排...
Beefsteak...
那行
That is it.
接下来的六个月 你去后院露营!
You are camping out in the backyard
for the next six months.
好的 合情合理 非常公平
Okay. Okay.
Very reasonable. That's more than fair.
It's going to be great. Thank you.
- 这会很棒的 谢谢 - 完美
-  Perfect. -  Thank you.
I don't understand.
我不明白 这是怎么回事?
How did this happen?
我发现你所做的事之后 非常生气
Well...
When I found out what you did, I was pissed.
我跟你说我要把这个故事 推给了MFMBC只是为了搞你
I told you I sold the story to MFMBC just to fuck with you.
But when Ricky was hired at Summerhayes, I thought,
但瑞奇被萨默海耶斯雇佣时
我心想:“等等 也许这真的会成为一个好故事”
wait a minute, maybe there actually is a story here.
So I pitched it to my producer at Channel 6.
所以我把它推给了第六频道的制作人
他们跟MFMBC的朋友说了这事 对方同意了我的提案
They told their friend at MFMBC
and they gave me the green light.
所有那些谎言 艾琳...
All those lies, Erin...
Can you ever forgive me?
你能原谅我吗?
原谅你当然没那么容易
It's definitely not going to be easy.
但...这有所帮助
But...
...this helps.
I had everything.
我曾经拥有一切 我曾经拥有好朋友 好工作
I had good friends. I had a great job.
The most kind-hearted,
世界上最善良 也是最漂亮的人爱着我
beautiful person in the whole world loved me.
Erin's the best thing that ever happened to me.
遇见艾琳是我这一生最美好的事
Ricky sent it to me today.
瑞奇今天给我发了这段录音
Here we go, here we go, here we go...
- 到了 - 那是谁?
Who's that?
Ricky! Look out!
瑞奇 小心!
-  -
结果如你所料吗 蠢货?
Did that go how you thought it would, wanker?!
Here, Rimestead! You've officially been served.
给你 莱姆斯特德 这个正式交给你了
什么...
What the...?
这是什么?
What's this?
这是比利艾道尔给的 强制停止令 好吗?
This is a cease-and-desist order from Billy Idol.
Yeah?
如果你再用恶心的歌词 玷污他的任何一首歌
If you disgrace any of his songs
with your disgusting lyrics ever again,
我们会把你告上法庭 懂了吗?
we'll see you in court.
Huh?
Yeah.
比利艾道尔看了我的演出?
So Billy Idol saw my act?
Fuck off!
去你的
太棒了!
Sweet!
More champagne, everyone!
大家再喝点香槟吗?
Billy Idol!
比利艾道尔
♪ I'm depending on you ♪
♪ Everything that you do ♪
♪ And I'm depending on you ♪
♪ Yeah, to see me through ♪
♪ You know that I love you... ♪
Is this Al Green?
这是艾尔格林吗?
It's Otis Redding.
是奥蒂斯雷丁
Was Otis Redding blind?
- 奥蒂斯雷丁是瞎子吗? - 不是
- No. - You sure?
你确定?他听上去像是个瞎子
- He sounds blind. - He does sound blind.
- 他确实听起来是个瞎子 - 他不是瞎子
He wasn't...
我要一杯蔓越莓汁 纯的
I'll take a... cranberry juice.
Neat. And a plate of your crispiest calamari.
还要一盘最脆的鱿鱼圈 史诗般的夜晚 对吧 各位?
- Epic night, am I right, guys? -  Yeah.
- 是啊 伙计 - 是啊
瑞奇 过来
Ricky! Get over here.
Oh!
Time to go bump and grind with my fiancée.
是时候跟我的未婚妻一起跳贴身舞了
- 你开玩笑的吧? - 真的
You're kidding, right?
Yeah.
But I don't know, who knows, right?
我不知道 谁知道呢?
Oh, hey, keep Saturday afternoon open.
嘿 周六下午空出来 我们有很多工作要做
We got a ton of work to do.
周六下午工作?
- Work on a Saturday? - Yeah, I signed us up.
对 我已经给我们报名了 我们要去帮忙清理纳拉甘西特湾
We're going to help clean up Narragansett Bay.
好的 兄弟
Yeah, man.
我没跟你们开玩笑 我们要去清理那些垃圾
I'm not messing with you. We're cleaning that shit up.
伙计
Man.
敬瑞奇斯坦尼奇
To Ricky Stanicky.
我们拥有过的最好的朋友
The best friend we ever had.
♪ In my head In my head ♪
♪ I am different in my head ♪
♪ I am someone else instead ♪
♪ In my head In my head ♪
♪ In my mind In my mind ♪
♪ There is sadness All the time ♪
♪ And I keep the things I find ♪
♪ In my mind In my mind ♪
♪ And never do I share These things with anyone ♪
♪ The feeling is cold And I'm afraid ♪
♪ Strangers passing, mmm ♪
♪ In my dream In my dream ♪
我爱你
♪ There are symbols That repeat ♪
再见
♪ There are copies In the street ♪
《圣诞老人的幸运鸡巴》
♪ In my dream In my dream ♪
♪ And never do I share These things with anyone ♪
♪ The feeling is cold And I'm afraid ♪
♪ Strangers passing, mmm. ♪
♪ Well, now, my engine's Overheating ♪
♪ A summer traffic jam ♪
♪ I'll be late for work again ♪
♪ But I'm doing The best that I can ♪
♪ Don't you look away, baby ♪
♪ My life just ain't What it seems ♪
♪ I got such big dreams, baby ♪
♪ My heart's busting At the seams ♪
♪ Everybody wants A day in the sun ♪
♪ Like gold tequila Shooting summer fun ♪
♪ I wanna be your number one ♪
♪ Your son of a gun ♪
♪ Everybody wants A day in the sun ♪
♪ Don't try to tell me That my race is run ♪
♪ Nothing's over, baby Nothing done ♪
♪ 'Til we have won Everybody wants one ♪
♪ Day in the sun ♪
♪ Day in the sun With you, baby ♪
♪ Day in the sun with you ♪
♪ Piece of work In progress, baby ♪
♪ But I'm trying not To let it show ♪
♪ You're my dream Come true, baby ♪
♪ A dream I can't let go ♪
♪ Everybody wants A day in the sun ♪
♪ Like gold tequila Shooting summer fun ♪
♪ I wanna be your number one ♪
♪ Your son of a gun ♪
♪ Everybody wants A day in the sun ♪
♪ Don't try to tell me That my race is run ♪
♪ Nothing's over, baby Nothing done ♪
♪ 'Til we have won Everybody wants one ♪
♪ Day in the sun ♪
♪ Day in the sun With you, baby ♪
♪ Day in the sun with you ♪
♪ Day in the sun with you. ♪
在此之前 我想说...
Before I get to that, I would like to say this.
♪ I like bigger, I like smaller I can do both ♪
♪ I like dinosaurs And I like woke ♪
♪ That's what we have to do ♪
♪ Some people say you can't But you, and you, me ♪
♪ All of us Together we can stand ♪
♪ We'll have bigger We'll have smaller ♪
♪ We can do both Do both ♪
♪ We like dinosaurs ♪
♪ And we like woke Like woke ♪
♪ To heck with the naysayers ♪
♪ I say we can ♪
♪ We will be able to narrow Maintain and expand ♪
♪ We are sharks ♪
♪ Why? ♪
♪ If we don't move forward We die ♪
♪ We'll have bigger We'll have smaller ♪
♪ We can do both Do both ♪
♪ We like dinosaurs ♪
♪ And we like woke Like woke ♪
♪ To heck with the naysayers ♪
♪ I say we can ♪
♪ We will be able to narrow Maintain and expand ♪
♪ We can do both. ♪
字幕翻译:匡思颖
创意监督 肖雪
黑夜里的一道冷光 于阴历 甲辰年 端月二十七 酉时
Powered by Bash Shell Script Merge Bilingual Subtitle ver 4.9